<odoo>
    <data>
        <record id="history" model="ir.ui.view">
            <field name="name">History</field>
            <field name="type">qweb</field>
            <field name="key">emea_college_theme.history</field>
            <field name="arch" type="xml">
                <t name="job-1" t-name="emea_college_theme.history_menu">
                    <t t-call="website.layout">
                        <div id="wrap" class="oe_structure">
                            <section class=" page">
                                <h2 class="page_head">HISTORY OF EMEA COLLEGE</h2>
                                <div class="page_text">
                                    EMEA College of Arts and Science, Kondotti is fast emerging as a resourceful
                                    destination
                                    for higher studies in Malabar, spreading the fragrance of education in the society.
                                    This
                                    college is affiliated to the University of Calicut. The college offers up-to-date,
                                    advanced, and job-oriented programmes in the vast expanding horizon of humanities,
                                    commerece, and science and technology. The college is situated at Kumminiparamba in
                                    Kondotti, 6 KMs away from University of Calicut, 2 KMs from Calicut International
                                    Airport, 18 KMs from Feroke Railway Station, and 32 KMs from Calicut City; with a
                                    congenial atmosphere for academic pursuits. The place is ideally suited for the
                                    growth
                                    and development of educational institutions for higher learning. The institution
                                    aims at
                                    the over all development of this backward area of Kerala by opening new vistas of
                                    opportunities to the future generations, without any discrimination against caste,
                                    creed, sex or colour. The college is run by Ernad Muslim Educational Association,
                                    which
                                    was formed with the objective of establishing a chain of educational institutions
                                    and
                                    cultural centres to cater to the needs of educationally and culturally backward
                                    section
                                    of the community. The college is a stepping stone to realize the objectives
                                    envisaged by
                                    the Association. Established on 1st November 1982 as a junior college, it flourished
                                    as
                                    a post graduate college today.
                                </div>
                            </section>
                        </div>
                    </t>
                </t>
            </field>
        </record>
        <record id="history_page" model="website.page">
            <field name="url">/history</field>
            <field name="is_published">True</field>
            <field name="view_id" ref="history"/>
            <field name="track">True</field>
        </record>
    </data>
</odoo>