<odoo>
    <data>
        <record id="principal" model="ir.ui.view">
            <field name="name">Principal</field>
            <field name="type">qweb</field>
            <field name="key">emea_college_theme.principal</field>
            <field name="arch" type="xml">
                <t t-name="emea_college_theme.principal_menu">
                    <t t-call="website.layout">
                        <div id="wrap" class="oe_structure">
                            <section class=" page pt32 pb32">
                                <h2 class="page_head">PRINCIPAL’S MESSAGE</h2>
                                <div class="align-center container pt32" style="max-width: 1320px;">
                                    <div class="row">
                                        <div class="col-md-12 col-lg-3 ">
                                            <div class="image-wrapper" id="prince_page">
                                                <img src="/emea_college_theme/static/img/princi.jpg"
                                                     id="prince_img"/>
                                                <h2 class="notes_head" style="font-size: 18px;   padding-bottom: 0;">Dr.
                                                    Abdul Muneer V
                                                </h2>
                                                <a href="#" class="readmore">VIEW PROFILE</a>
                                            </div>

                                        </div>
                                        <div class="col-12 align-left col-lg-9 padding-0">
                                            <div class="card-wrapper prince_card">
                                                <p class="notes">
                                                    EMEA College of Arts and Science, Kondottti, was established as an
                                                    embodiment of a long cherished dream of people of Ernad, a backward
                                                    region in erstwhile Malabar District of British India. With the
                                                    illustrious aim of bringing the educationally deprived youth of the
                                                    region into the mainstream of education, the college came into
                                                    existence
                                                    in 1982 thanks to the efforts of visionary social leaders like
                                                    Sayyid
                                                    Mohammed Ali Shihab Thangal, Jb. P Seethi Haji Sahib, Jb. Avukader
                                                    Kutty
                                                    Naha Sahib, Jb. N.V Ibrahim Master, etc. The college is run by Ernad
                                                    Muslim Education Association, a registered society formed by a group
                                                    of
                                                    social reformers for establishing educational institutions to uplift
                                                    the
                                                    socially and economically backward populace of the region.
                                                    <br/>
                                                    Started in 1982 as a humble institution offering pre-degree courses
                                                    in
                                                    commerce and humanities, the college is now a full-fledged centre of
                                                    academic excellence providing five PG Programmes, eleven UG
                                                    Programmes
                                                    two BVoc Programmes and a PhD Programme in Economics. The college
                                                    was
                                                    accredited by NAAC with 'B++' grade in its first cycle of
                                                    accreditation
                                                    in 2005. Later in 2014, it was awarded with 'A' grade. And recently
                                                    in
                                                    2021, the college underwent the third cycle and got accredited with
                                                    'A'
                                                    grade (CGPA: 3.13)
                                                    <br/>
                                                    <br/>
                                                    EMEA College is now renowned for its excellence in academic
                                                    performance,
                                                    well-qualified faculty, state-of-the-art facilities, and curricular
                                                    and
                                                    co-curricular activities. The beautiful campus sprawls over twenty
                                                    acres
                                                    of land. That the college has all facilities and provisions for
                                                    enhancing the abilities of student community like SMST Memorial
                                                    Central
                                                    Library, science and computer science laboratories, Wi-Fi
                                                    connectivity,
                                                    research and publication facilities, audio visual theatre,
                                                    auditorium,
                                                    sports ground, gymnasium, hostels; NSS, SIP, NCC Units, Students
                                                    Union,
                                                    and the presence of other club activities make the college an ideal
                                                    campus that every student dreams of.
                                                    <br/>
                                                    <br/>
                                                    The support and guidance being extended by the philanthropic EMEA
                                                    management to the college and students are distinctive. Old Students
                                                    Association of EMEA (OSAEMEA), the alumni association is committed
                                                    to
                                                    the betterment of their alma mater and contributes immensely to its
                                                    infrastructural and academic growth. The activities and
                                                    contributions of
                                                    the college PTA are unparalleled. The Shihab Thangal Memorial Merit
                                                    Scholarship it instituted is the best example.
                                                    <br/>
                                                    The college has always promoted the sports and arts activities of
                                                    the
                                                    students. The Physical Education Department has won myriad of state
                                                    and
                                                    national level championships in football, weightlifting, Wushu, and
                                                    volleyball.
                                                    <br/>
                                                    Being a temple of learning, the college is committed to provide
                                                    quality
                                                    education, and to help students chase and achieve their aspirations
                                                    along with fostering good nature, discipline, respect and
                                                    responsibility
                                                    within them and thereby moulding them into useful individuals for
                                                    their
                                                    family and society.
                                                    <br/>Let us do the best.<br/>Thank you.
                                                    <br/>
                                                    <br/>
                                                    <span style="font-weight:bold;">Contact Info:</span>
                                                    <br/>
                                                    Email: principal@emeacollege.ac.in
                                                    <br/>
                                                    Phone : 0483 271 3530
                                                </p>
                                            </div>
                                        </div>

                                    </div>
                                </div>
                            </section>
                        </div>
                    </t>
                </t>
            </field>
        </record>
        <record id="principal_page" model="website.page">
            <field name="url">/principal</field>
            <field name="is_published">True</field>
            <field name="view_id" ref="principal"/>
            <field name="track">True</field>
        </record>
    </data>
</odoo>