<odoo>
    <data>
        <record id="about_mes" model="ir.ui.view">
            <field name="name">About MES</field>
            <field name="type">qweb</field>
            <field name="key">mes_college.about_mes</field>
            <field name="arch" type="xml">
                <t name="english" t-name="mes_college.about_menu">
                    <t t-call="website.layout">
                        <div id="wrap" class="oe_structure">
                            <section class="bg_color">
                                <div class="container" style="max-width: 95%;">
                                    <h2 class="main-head" id="title">About MES</h2>
                                    <div class=" row pt32 pb32" >
                                        <section class="col-md-8">
                                            <div class="pb32">
                                                <img src="/mes_college/static/img/banner.jpg" class="w-100 h-100"
                                                     style="min-height:400px;object-fit: fill;filter: brightness(0.8);"/>
                                            </div>
                                            <div>
                                                <div class="content_text">
                                                    MES Kalladi College, is the proud symbol of the Muslim Educational
                                                    Society
                                                    to the cause of higher education in Kerala, especially to the
                                                    educationally
                                                    and socially backward sections. This is the first college started by
                                                    the
                                                    MES
                                                    and it is also the felicitous outcome of the noble endeavor of the
                                                    late
                                                    Kalladi Cheriya Kunhammed Sahib and the local public. College is
                                                    located
                                                    in
                                                    a vast area, in the backdrops of Western Ghats. The college started
                                                    functioning as a junior college in 1967 and was upgraded in 1971
                                                    with
                                                    the
                                                    introduction of degree courses and later the college was further
                                                    upgraded as
                                                    a Post Graduate college in 1978. Now the college is offering 20
                                                    Under
                                                    Graduate programmes, 9 Post Graduate programmes, 1 Integrated
                                                    programme
                                                    and
                                                    4 Research Programmes.
                                                    <br/>

                                                    The College is equipped with good infrastructural and technological
                                                    facilities to enhance the academic environment. All the classrooms
                                                    are
                                                    fully
                                                    ICT enabled with either interactive panel or LCD projector. The
                                                    laboratories
                                                    are well equipped to support the academic activities. The college
                                                    has an
                                                    automated library which serves as a platform for knowledge enriching
                                                    and
                                                    sharing. It is equipped with sufficient number of books and
                                                    journals.
                                                    The
                                                    research activities of the college are commendable. The faculty
                                                    members
                                                    and
                                                    research scholars have publications in international peer reviewed
                                                    journals.
                                                    Along with the curricular and academic enrichment of the students,
                                                    college
                                                    focuses on the skill development of the students thereby mould them
                                                    to
                                                    achieve better career goals. College is offering foreign language
                                                    training
                                                    which helps the students in acquiring better opportunities in
                                                    foreign
                                                    countries. Vocational degree programmes like B.Voc Diary Science
                                                    &amp;
                                                    Technology, Data Science &amp; Analytics and Tourism &amp;
                                                    Hospitality
                                                    Management
                                                    gave the students a platform to complete a degree programme along
                                                    with
                                                    enhancing skill in that specific area.
                                                    <br/>
                                                    The college has a keen interest in providing various services to the
                                                    society
                                                    along with the students’ wholistic development. College organizes
                                                    outreach
                                                    and extension programmes to cater its services to the community. The
                                                    extension programmes mainly focus on the local community. Awareness
                                                    programmes, training programmes, skill development programmes and
                                                    cleaning
                                                    activities are organized to the benefit of the society. The medical
                                                    centre
                                                    established as a social welfare project of our college and an
                                                    affiliate
                                                    and
                                                    peripheral centre of MES Medical College intents to give medical
                                                    care
                                                    and
                                                    assistance to the students and local community.
                                                    <br/>
                                                    College provides helping hand to the nearby tribal area, Attapadi. A
                                                    health
                                                    centre functioning in the Attappadi area provides proper medical
                                                    assistance
                                                    in the form of medical checkups, health awareness programmes etc.
                                                    College
                                                    promotes the talents of students in sports and arts by providing
                                                    them
                                                    with
                                                    the facilities to enhance their abilities. The college has a playing
                                                    ground
                                                    with 400 mtr track and an indoor stadium to promote the sports and
                                                    games
                                                    related activities. Our students achieved many national and
                                                    international
                                                    medals in various sports activities such as Karate, Thaikonda,
                                                    Wrestling,
                                                    athletics, football, kick boxing, etc. The college has a legacy of
                                                    great
                                                    sports achievement in its history. Every year our students bring
                                                    laurels
                                                    to
                                                    the college by achieving medals in sports. Our students mark their
                                                    merit
                                                    in
                                                    arts by achieving prizes in University Festivals. MES Kalladi
                                                    College
                                                    has a
                                                    long history of contributing to the educational and cultural
                                                    upliftment
                                                    of
                                                    the community. It is continuously in pursuit of excellence by
                                                    adapting
                                                    with
                                                    the new trends in higher education.

                                                </div>
                                            </div>
                                        </section>
                                        <div class="col-md-3">
                                            <section class="naac_link">
                                                <a href="/vision_mission" class="readmore" id="naac_link">Vision And
                                                    Mission
                                                    <span class="fa fa-long-arrow-right text-o-color-3"
                                                          data-bs-original-title=""
                                                          title="" aria-describedby="tooltip544395"></span>
                                                </a>
                                                <a href="/vision_mission"
                                                   class="readmore" id="naac_link" target="_blank">Core Values
                                                    <span class="fa fa-long-arrow-right text-o-color-3"
                                                          data-bs-original-title=""
                                                          title="" aria-describedby="tooltip544395"></span>
                                                </a>
                                                <a href="/brief_history" class="readmore" id="naac_link">Brief History
                                                    <span class="fa fa-long-arrow-right text-o-color-3"
                                                          data-bs-original-title=""
                                                          title="" aria-describedby="tooltip544395"></span>
                                                </a>
                                                <a href="/milestone" class="readmore" id="naac_link">Milestone
                                                    <span class="fa fa-long-arrow-right text-o-color-3"
                                                          data-bs-original-title=""
                                                          title="" aria-describedby="tooltip544395"></span>
                                                </a>
                                                <a href="/college_crest" class="readmore" id="naac_link">College Crest
                                                    <span class="fa fa-long-arrow-right text-o-color-3"
                                                          data-bs-original-title=""
                                                          title="" aria-describedby="tooltip544395"></span>
                                                </a>

                                            </section>

                                        </div>
                                    </div>
                                </div>
                            </section>
                        </div>
                    </t>
                </t>
            </field>
        </record>
        <record id="about_mes_page" model="website.page">
            <field name="url">/about_mes</field>
            <field name="is_published">True</field>
            <field name="view_id" ref="about_mes"/>
            <field name="track">True</field>
        </record>
    </data>
</odoo>