<odoo>
    <data>
        <record id="brief_history_mes" model="ir.ui.view">
            <field name="name">Brief History</field>
            <field name="type">qweb</field>
            <field name="key">mes_college.brief_history_mes</field>
            <field name="arch" type="xml">
                <t name="Brief History" t-name="mes_college.brief_history_menu">
                    <t t-call="website.layout">
                        <div id="wrap" class="oe_structure">
                            <section class="bg_color">
                                <div class="container" style="max-width: 95%;">
                                    <h2 class="main-head" id="title">Brief History</h2>
                                    <div class=" pt32 pb32" style="padding:15px;">
                                        <section class="col-md-12" style="margin:auto;">
                                            <div>
                                                <div class="content_text">
                                                    MES Kalladi College, Mannarkkad is the proud symbol of the Muslim
                                                    Educational Society, Calicut to the cause of higher education in
                                                    Kerala, especially to the educationally backward areas of Malabar.
                                                    This is the first college started by the MES and it is also the
                                                    felicitous outcome of the noble endeavor of the late Kalladi Cheriya
                                                    Kunhammed Sahib and the local public. College is located in a vast
                                                    area, a major part of which was donated by the late Janab Valayadi
                                                    Kunhayammu Haji.
                                                    The college is situated 2 km away from Mannarkkad town on the side
                                                    of Palakkad – Calicut National Highway and bordered by the perennial
                                                    river “Kunthipuzha” and fortressed by panoramic hills of Silent
                                                    Valley and Attappadi.
                                                    The college started functioning as a junior college in 1967 and was
                                                    upgraded in 1971 with the introduction of degree courses in History,
                                                    Economics, Mathematics, Botany and Commerce. Further it was upgraded
                                                    as a Post Graduate college in 1978 with the introduction of M.Com.
                                                    The college was accredited by NAAC at B++ grade in 2004 and at A
                                                    grade in 2013.
                                                    The FIST funding form Department of Science and Technology, Govt. of
                                                    India received in 2015.The departments of History and Chemistry have
                                                    been upgraded as Research Centres in 2016 and 2017 respectively, and
                                                    are equipped with Modern Laboratories, Research Halls and Research
                                                    Cubicles. The college was accredited at A+ grade in the third cycle
                                                    by NAAC in 2019.
                                                    The Five Year Integrated PG programme in Forensic Science started in
                                                    2020 and B Voc programmes introduced in 2021.


                                                </div>
                                            </div>
                                        </section>
                                    </div>
                                </div>
                            </section>
                        </div>
                    </t>
                </t>
            </field>
        </record>
        <record id="brief_history_mes_page" model="website.page">
            <field name="url">/brief_history</field>
            <field name="is_published">True</field>
            <field name="view_id" ref="brief_history_mes"/>
            <field name="track">True</field>
        </record>
    </data>
</odoo>