<odoo>
    <data>
        <record id="code_of_conduct_students" model="ir.ui.view">
            <field name="name">Code Of Conduct Students</field>
            <field name="type">qweb</field>
            <field name="key">mes_college.code_of_conduct_students</field>
            <field name="arch" type="xml">
                <t name="graduate-attribute" t-name="mes_college.code_of_conduct_students_menu">
                    <t t-call="website.layout">
                        <div id="wrap" class="oe_structure">
                            <section class="bg_color">
                                <div class="container" style="max-width: 95%;">
                                    <h2 class="main-head" id="title">Code Of Conduct Students</h2>
                                    <div class=" pt32 pb32" style="padding:15px;">
                                        <section class="col-md-12" style="margin:auto;">
                                            <div>
                                                <div class="content_text">
                                                    The Code of conduct of the college are formed by the management and
                                                    the Principal accordance with Government and University rules to
                                                    ensure a peaceful campus atmosphere.
                                                    <ul>
                                                        <li>
                                                            In the light of the judgments of the Honorable High Court of
                                                            Kerala [2003(2) KLT 582, WP(C) No. 986/2018/(W)], the
                                                            college has prohibited all political activism within the
                                                            college campus. Activities such as Demonstration, Campaign,
                                                            Vandalism, Display of Poster, Banners, Flag, Strike, Gherao,
                                                            Dharna, Hartal are prohibited.
                                                        </li>
                                                        <li>
                                                            As per the judgment in RP 435/03 by the Honorable High Court
                                                            of Kerala and the directives of the Registrar of University
                                                            of Calicut No. L.C. SW (2) College Union Election /OP/04
                                                            dated 02-03-05 to this effect, the Management of the College
                                                            has the right to hold the union election in the
                                                            Parliamentary form or any other manner it deems right for
                                                            the maintenance of discipline in the campus.
                                                        </li>
                                                        <li>
                                                            Students of M.E.S. Kalladi college, Mannarkkad shall try
                                                            their best to uphold the honor and prestige of the
                                                            institution by humanity, fellow feeling, and hard work. They
                                                            should endeavor to create an atmosphere conducive to
                                                            academic, cultural, and social progress.
                                                        </li>
                                                        <li>
                                                            Students must observe strict discipline in the campus,
                                                            behave with dignity and courtesy to the principal, faculty
                                                            members, administrative staff, visitors, and fellow
                                                            students.
                                                        </li>
                                                        <li>
                                                            Class hours are from 9:30 am to 3:15 pm. Be in time for
                                                            classes. Day scholars are not expected to be present on the
                                                            campus after 4:00 pm.
                                                        </li>
                                                        <li>
                                                            Once students are admitted to the college, they are bound by
                                                            the code of conduct laid down by the college through the
                                                            college calendar.
                                                        </li>
                                                        <li>
                                                            Students should come to the campus wearing the stipulated
                                                            uniform only. On special occasions, students are exempted
                                                            from uniform only with the permission of the principal. But
                                                            only formal dressing will be allowed on the campus. Casual
                                                            dressing / specially designed / gang dress / extra color /
                                                            special dressing will not be permitted.
                                                        </li>
                                                        <li>
                                                            Staff members/Discipline Committee shall have the powers to
                                                            deny admission to students to
                                                            classes/office/labs/library/meetings/cultural programs in
                                                            the case of violation of the dress code of the college.
                                                        </li>
                                                        <li>
                                                            No students shall always wear identity cards issued by the
                                                            college with a tag and show them as and when demanded by the
                                                            Principal, teachers, and office staff/security staff.
                                                        </li>
                                                        <li>
                                                            Political activism is strictly banned in the campus.
                                                            Students are forbidden to organize or attend meetings other
                                                            than the official ones. Students resorting to strikes are
                                                            prohibited from entering the verandah of the building or the
                                                            classroom.
                                                        </li>
                                                        <li>
                                                            No students shall use or keep in possession alcoholic drinks
                                                            or drugs. Using/keeping of these items will lead to
                                                            immediate expulsion of the students from the college and
                                                            hostels.
                                                        </li>
                                                        <li>
                                                            Students are not allowed to organize or attend any meeting
                                                            in the college or collect money for any purpose without the
                                                            written permission of the Principal. Outsiders are not
                                                            allowed to attend or organize any program inside the campus.
                                                        </li>
                                                        <li>
                                                            The principal shall have the power to inflict the following
                                                            punishments; fine, cancellation of attendance, withholding
                                                            of term certificate, forfeiture of educational concession
                                                            and scholarships, suspension, rustication from one or more
                                                            semesters, expulsion, compulsory issue of TC etc.
                                                        </li>
                                                        <li>
                                                            Irregular attendance, insubordination to teachers, habitual
                                                            inattention to class work, obscenity in word or act are
                                                            sufficient reasons for the permanent or temporary dismissal
                                                            of a student.
                                                        </li>
                                                        <li>
                                                            Students should keep vigilance on timely notifications and
                                                            announcements. Failure / ignorance will not be an excuse.
                                                        </li>
                                                        <li>
                                                            Banners, flags, Poster, etc. shall not allowed inside the
                                                            campus or at the gates or compound walls without the
                                                            permission of the Principal.
                                                        </li>
                                                        <li>
                                                            Students who are charged with a criminal offense and are
                                                            under suspension shall not be allowed to enter the campus
                                                            without permission.
                                                        </li>
                                                        <li>
                                                            Students are allowed to bring vehicles into the campus with
                                                            the prior permission. They have to park their vehicle at the
                                                            allotted place at their own risk. Stunting and racing of
                                                            vehicles within and in a radius of 200 meters outside the
                                                            campus are strictly banned. Students and staff have to
                                                            register their vehicle number and license number with the
                                                            security.
                                                        </li>
                                                        <li>
                                                            Disfiguring of walls, damaging of fittings and fixtures,
                                                            attracts fine or disciplinary actions. Collective fines will
                                                            be imposed for any damage if the cause cannot be traced to
                                                            any individual.
                                                        </li>
                                                        <li>
                                                            Students are strictly prohibited from using mobile phones in
                                                            the College Campus. If students are found using mobile
                                                            phones on the campus, their phones would be confiscated and
                                                            serious action taken against them.
                                                        </li>
                                                        <li>
                                                            Daily absentee reports, and other important messages are
                                                            sent as SMS alerts to the parent's mobile number.
                                                        </li>
                                                        <li>
                                                            Cinematic dance, DJ, Fashion show, and birthday parties
                                                            shall not be allowed inside the college campus.
                                                        </li>
                                                        <li>
                                                            Ragging is a criminal offense and its any form should be
                                                            seriously dealt. To register the complaint regarding the
                                                            ragging by students should be within 24 hours and, the
                                                            action will be taken within the next 24 hours. Help line:
                                                            1800-180-5522. Website: helpsite@antiragging.net
                                                        </li>
                                                    </ul>

                                                </div>
                                            </div>
                                        </section>
                                    </div>
                                </div>
                            </section>
                        </div>
                    </t>
                </t>
            </field>
        </record>
        <record id="code_of_conduct_students_page" model="website.page">
            <field name="url">/code_of_conduct_students</field>
            <field name="is_published">True</field>
            <field name="view_id" ref="code_of_conduct_students"/>
            <field name="track">True</field>
        </record>
    </data>
</odoo>