<odoo>
    <data>
        <record id="principal_mes" model="ir.ui.view">
            <field name="name">Principal</field>
            <field name="type">qweb</field>
            <field name="key">mes_college.principal_mes</field>
            <field name="arch" type="xml">
                <t name="principal" t-name="mes_college.principal_menu">
                    <t t-call="website.layout">
                        <div id="wrap" class="oe_structure">
                            <section class="bg_color">
                                <div class="container" style="max-width: 95%;">
                                    <h2 class="main-head" id="title">Principal</h2>
                                </div>

                                <section class="section3" style="">
                                    <div class=" prince_container pt32" style="height:950px;">
                                        <div class="row">
                                            <div class="col-md-3  my-auto padding-0 o_colored_level prince_block">
                                                <div class="image-wrapper">
                                                    <img src="/mes_college/static/img/Rajesh.jpeg" class="prince-img"
                                                         loading="lazy"
                                                         style=""/>
                                                    <h2 class="faculty_name" style="text-align:center;">
                                                        Dr. C Rajesh
                                                    </h2>
                                                    <div class="designation" style="padding-bottom: 10px">M.Sc., Ph.D.</div>
                                                    <a href="/faculty_profile" class="readmore" id="principal_read">View
                                                        Profile
                                                        <span class="fa fa-long-arrow-right text-o-color-3"
                                                              contenteditable="false"
                                                              data-bs-original-title="" title=""
                                                              aria-describedby="tooltip544395">
                                                        </span>
                                                    </a>
                                                </div>
                                            </div>
                                            <div class="col-md-9 align-left padding-0 o_colored_level principal_block">
                                                <div class="text_1">As we stand on the threshold of our institution's
                                                    56th
                                                    year, I feel honoured and privileged to reflect on the incredible
                                                    journey of this institution, since its establishment in 1967. The
                                                    enduring legacy of five decades serves as a testimony to our
                                                    unwavering
                                                    commitment and significant contributions to education. Nestled in
                                                    the
                                                    heart of ethereal land of natural beauty, our college has not only
                                                    weathered the winds of time but has also thrived, becoming a beacon
                                                    of
                                                    academic and holistic excellence.
                                                    The journey from our inception to the present day mirrors a
                                                    continuous
                                                    pursuit of excellence in curricular, co-curricular, and
                                                    extracurricular
                                                    realms. The evolution of the college, from an undergraduate
                                                    institution
                                                    to encompassing research departments, defines our academic feats.
                                                    The
                                                    dedication and commitment of our esteemed faculty infuse vitality
                                                    and
                                                    creativity into academic pursuits, concurrently aligning with our
                                                    vision
                                                    of continual progress and ambitious goals.
                                                    The success of our college is not merely quantifiable in years;
                                                    rather,
                                                    it is encapsulated in the myriad stories of triumph, growth, and
                                                    learning that echo within our classrooms and resonate across our
                                                    campus.
                                                    The unwavering support of the management has been instrumental in
                                                    fostering the conductive environment of growth and success of this
                                                    institution. I extend my heartfelt gratitude to every member of our
                                                    college community—students, faculty, staff, and alumni—for their
                                                    staunch
                                                    support and dedication. As we embark on the journey ahead, let us
                                                    continue to embrace innovation, uphold academic rigor, and foster a
                                                    culture of inclusivity. Together, let us build on the legacy of the
                                                    past
                                                    and chart a course for an even brighter future.
                                                    <br/>
                                                    <span>Thank you for being an integral part of our
                                                        remarkable journey.
                                                    </span>

                                                </div>
                                            </div>
                                        </div>
                                    </div>
                                </section>
                            </section>
                        </div>
                    </t>
                </t>
            </field>
        </record>
        <record id="principal_mes_page" model="website.page">
            <field name="url">/principal</field>
            <field name="is_published">True</field>
            <field name="view_id" ref="principal_mes"/>
            <field name="track">True</field>
        </record>
    </data>
</odoo>