<odoo>
    <data>
        <record id="resource_mobilization_mes" model="ir.ui.view">
            <field name="name">Resource Mobilization Policy</field>
            <field name="type">qweb</field>
            <field name="key">mes_college.resource_mobilization_mes</field>
            <field name="arch" type="xml">
                <t name="english" t-name="mes_college.resource_mobilization_menu">
                    <t t-call="website.layout">
                        <div id="wrap" class="oe_structure">
                            <section class="bg_color">
                                <div class="container" id="container_width">
                                    <section class="col-md-12" style="margin:auto;">
                                        <h2 class="main-head"
                                            style="text-align: left;padding-left: 20px;padding-top:20px;">Resource
                                            Mobilization Policy
                                        </h2>
                                        <div class="content_text">
                                            The Institution has a transparent and well-planned financial management
                                            system. The major source of funding is from state and central government in
                                            addition to the revenue generated through fee collection. The Resource
                                            mobilization policy focuses on achieving the goals and target of the
                                            institution ensuring accountability and transparency. The harmonized
                                            Governing body coordinates and monitors the optimal utilization of the funds
                                            for the promotion of learner-centric ecosystem.

                                            <ul>
                                                <li>
                                                    The Institution is a centrally managed non-profit organization with
                                                    honorary governing body members which ensures the income generated
                                                    is spent optimally in the institution itself
                                                </li>
                                                <li>
                                                    A financial advisory body is in place to manage the managed funds.
                                                    The government funds are taken care of by the Planning forum, UGC
                                                    plan coordinator and DST-FIST coordinator of the college
                                                </li>
                                                <li>
                                                    Funds are provided to meet the infrastructure requirement of the
                                                    institution while starting new programmes and centers
                                                </li>
                                                <li>
                                                    The management provides financial supports to
                                                    seminars/workshops/expert talks/Association activities/Faculty
                                                    Development programmes
                                                </li>
                                                <li>
                                                    The extracurricular activities of the students are a major concern
                                                    and adequate funds provide for Sports and Cultural activities
                                                </li>
                                                <li>
                                                    Scholarships and free ships to the deserving students
                                                </li>
                                                <li>
                                                    Provident fund(PF) and Employee State Insurance(ESI) benefits are
                                                    provided to the Management appointed staffs
                                                </li>
                                                <li>
                                                    Tuition fee and Corporate grant are used for the infrastructure
                                                    development and academic activities Government funds are optimally
                                                    used for which it is sanctioned Transparency and accountability is
                                                    ensured by conducting annual financial audits

                                                </li>
                                                <li>
                                                    Hostel Fee
                                                </li>
                                                <li>
                                                    Government funds-UGC/DST/Grant-in-Aid of Kerala Government

                                                </li>
                                                <li>
                                                    Grants From individuals, philanthropist
                                                </li>
                                                <li>
                                                    College Development Fund
                                                </li>
                                                <li>
                                                    Alumni Contribution
                                                </li>
                                                <li>
                                                    Central development fund
                                                </li>
                                                <li>
                                                    Tuition fee and Corporate grant is used for the infrastructure and
                                                    academic activities
                                                </li>
                                                <li>
                                                    Government funds are optimally used for which it is sanctioned
                                                </li>
                                                <li>
                                                    Transparency and accountability is ensured by conducting an annual
                                                    audit of the statements
                                                </li>
                                                <li>
                                                    Financial support provided by the government agencies are audited by
                                                    the respective Government Departments
                                                </li>

                                            </ul>
                                            <div>
                                                <strong>Financial Audit of Grant : Grants and funds sanctioned by
                                                    Government/UGC :
                                                </strong>
                                                There are their levels of audit for the funds
                                                sanctioned by the Government. They are as follows:
                                            </div>
                                            <ol>
                                                <li>
                                                    Chartered Accountant-After a stipulated period of time, the accounts
                                                    for all the grants and funds sanctioned by the Government/UGC are
                                                    initially submitted to an external Chartered Accountant. The audit
                                                    report issued by the auditor with utilization certificate and all
                                                    necessary ratified accounts are submitted to the concerned
                                                    sanctioned authorities.
                                                </li>
                                                <li>
                                                    Directorate of Collegiate Education-At the time of annual audits by
                                                    the Directorate of Collegiate Education, the audit team verifies all
                                                    the financial documents related to the public funds utilized by
                                                    College. After hearing the clarifications and corrections, the final
                                                    accounts are settled.
                                                </li>
                                                <li>
                                                    Accountant General, Kerala-The Accountant General, Kerala also
                                                    conduct their periodic verification of all the accounts sanctioned
                                                    by the Government. Their suggestions and directions are also
                                                    incorporated in the further utilization of the funds.
                                                </li>
                                            </ol>
                                            <div>
                                                <strong>Grants and funds sanctioned by Management
                                                </strong>
                                            </div>
                                            <ol>
                                                <li>
                                                    The institution has a strong financial advisory board for Management
                                                    of accounts and all the accounts sanctioned are audited internally
                                                    as well as externally. On behalf of the Management, all daily
                                                    transactions are verified by the financial advisor of the college.
                                                </li>
                                                <li>
                                                    The internal audit of Management accounts is done by the Treasurer,
                                                    MES Central Committee, Calicut periodically. They verify all
                                                    financial transactions and submit a detailed report of observations
                                                    based on the observations given by internal auditor. The financial
                                                    advisor of the college modifies the statements of accounts.
                                                </li>
                                                <li>
                                                    The Management has appointed M. A. Moideen and Associates as the
                                                    external auditor of the Management accounts. At the end of every
                                                    financial year they prepare annual financial statements and audit
                                                    reports.
                                                </li>
                                            </ol>
                                        </div>
                                    </section>
                                </div>
                            </section>
                        </div>
                    </t>
                </t>
            </field>
        </record>
        <record id="resource_mobilization_mes_page" model="website.page">
            <field name="url">/resource_mobilization</field>
            <field name="is_published">True</field>
            <field name="view_id" ref="resource_mobilization_mes"/>
            <field name="track">True</field>
        </record>
    </data>
</odoo>