<odoo>
    <data>
        <record id="strategic_plan_mes" model="ir.ui.view">
            <field name="name">Strategic Plan</field>
            <field name="type">qweb</field>
            <field name="key">mes_college.strategic_plan_mes</field>
            <field name="arch" type="xml">
                <t name="english" t-name="mes_college.strategic_plan_menu">
                    <t t-call="website.layout">
                        <div id="wrap" class="oe_structure">
                            <section class="bg_color">
                                <div class="container" id="container_width">
                                    <div class=" pt32 pb32 col-md-8">
                                        <div>
                                            <h2 class="main-head" style="text-align: left;padding-left: 20px;">
                                                Strategic Plan
                                            </h2>
                                            <section class="d-flex o_colored_level margin_30 ssr"
                                                     style="background-image: none;">
                                                <div class="col-md-6 programme_link">
                                                    Strategic Plan 2020-2021
                                                </div>
                                                <a href="#"
                                                   target="_blank" class="readmore" id="view">View
                                                </a>
                                            </section>
                                        </div>
                                    </div>
                                    <section class="col-md-12" style="margin:auto;">
                                        <h2 class="main-head" style="text-align: left;padding-left: 20px;padding-top:20px;">Vision 2020
                                        </h2>
                                        <div class="content_text">
                                            M.E.S. Kalladi College, Mannarkkad is a Government Aided college is
                                            affiliated to University of Calicut. The college started functioning as a
                                            Junior College in 1967. University of Calicut permitted to start degree
                                            classes during 1971-72. The campus is situated in the Mannarkkad Panchayath
                                            on a beautiful hillock in the Palakkad-Calicut National Highway and is
                                            bordered by the perennial Kunthipuzha and fortressed by panoramic Attapadi
                                            hills.

                                            The college is the proud symbol of the Muslim Educational Society, which is
                                            one of the largest minority educational agency in India. This is the first
                                            college started by the MES to the cause of higher education in Kerala,
                                            especially to the educationally backward areas of Malabar. The vision and
                                            mission statement of the college are in tune with the objectives of the
                                            Higher Education Policy. The college offers seven UG programmes, six PG
                                            programmes and eight Certificate programmes. The administration implemented
                                            the Decentralized mechanism for quality improvement.

                                            A meeting of the Management with the Internal Quality Assurance Cell and
                                            Planning forum has been convened to formulate a strategic plan of the
                                            institution based on the NAAC Peer Team report on Institutional Re-
                                            accreditation of 22nd November, 2012 suggested recommendations for quality
                                            enhancement of the institution. The meeting analyzed the recommendations of
                                            the report in detail and thrust areas were identified to transform the
                                            institution to “Autonomous status and Potential of Excellence”. The areas
                                            identified by the meeting are Inclusive Excellence, Digital Campus, Building
                                            Students Ability, Research, Green Campus, Sports, Community Building and
                                            Infrastructure

                                            The meeting entrusted faculty members for monitoring the progress. There
                                            will be three level target achievement analysis Short term (2014-16J,
                                            Midterm (2016-18J and Vision accomplishment [2020). The funds required will
                                            be mobilized from Management and Government funding agencies.

                                            The strategic plan is signed on 20th March,2013
                                        </div>
                                    </section>
                                </div>
                            </section>
                        </div>
                    </t>
                </t>
            </field>
        </record>
        <record id="strategic_plan_mes_page" model="website.page">
            <field name="url">/strategic_plan</field>
            <field name="is_published">True</field>
            <field name="view_id" ref="strategic_plan_mes"/>
            <field name="track">True</field>
        </record>
    </data>
</odoo>