<odoo>
    <data>
        <record id="alumni_associates" model="ir.ui.view">
            <field name="name">alumni_associates</field>
            <field name="type">qweb</field>
            <field name="key">mes_college.alumni_associates</field>
            <field name="arch" type="xml">
                <t name="english" t-name="mes_college.alumni_associates_menu">
                    <t t-call="website.layout">
                        <div id="wrap" class="oe_structure">
                            <section class="bg_color">
                                <div class="container" id="container_width">
                                    <div class="row">
                                        <div class="col-md-9 pb16">
                                            <h2 class="main-head" style="text-align:left; padding-top:20px;">
                                                Alumni Association
                                            </h2>
                                            <div class="content_text" style="text-align:justify;padding: 0;">
                                                College is devoted to cherishing the relationship with our family
                                                members by
                                                constant touchups, interactions, and friendly get-together. Alumni of
                                                the
                                                college envision fostering friendly cooperation between present and old
                                                generation of our students thereby enhancing the betterment of the
                                                institution.
                                                Alumni associations of our college arrange to get together yearly on a
                                                departmental basis, where the members of MES Kalladi family gather
                                                together
                                                offering their vibrant involvement in all spheres of college activities.
                                                Annual
                                                alumni meet conducted on 2017 December 15 approved the bye-law regarding
                                                the
                                                registration of Alumni associations.
                                                <br/>
                                                <br/>
                                                The general alumni (MES KALLADI COLLEGE ALUMNI ASSOCIATION) is
                                                registered
                                                under
                                                the Societies Act of 1860 with No. PKD CA/101/2019, and is committed to
                                                renewing
                                                the registration as per rules. Annual alumni meet are conducted and
                                                office
                                                bearers of respective academic years are selected. Notifications
                                                regarding
                                                the
                                                Alumni meets are published in the leading newspapers as well as the
                                                concerned
                                                faculties in-charge used to send personal invitations to the alumni
                                                members
                                                using the possibilities of Social Media.
                                                <br/>
                                                <br/>
                                                The get together offers their valuable bits of advice and contributions
                                                on
                                                infrastructure, academic activities and overall development of the
                                                college.
                                                Alumni associations are dynamic in Kalladi premises where the warmth of
                                                togetherness is enjoyed and assured.
                                                <br/>
                                                <br/>
                                                The college conducts departmental level alumni meets, family
                                                get-together
                                                and
                                                annual family meets. Executive meetings of Departmental Alumni’s are
                                                conducted
                                                every year to ensure coordination and proper conduct of alumni
                                                gatherings.
                                                Every
                                                department keeps a separate register of their alumni members where their
                                                permanent address, phone number, and professional details are entered
                                                and
                                                the
                                                departments ensure to update the details every year. Alumni committee of
                                                each
                                                department is constituted under the charge of department head where
                                                present
                                                faculties, retired faculties and the alumni member of nearby locale are
                                                members.
                                                The college is committed towards the valuable feedback of alumni members
                                                which
                                                are effectively channelized for the better functioning and development
                                                of
                                                the
                                                college.
                                                <br/>
                                                <br/>
                                                All retired staffs are invited to the alumni gatherings and departments
                                                follow
                                                the practice of observing a day where a space of interaction with former
                                                faculties and present students of the college is offered. Financial and
                                                placement supports are given by alumni members to the needy students of
                                                the
                                                college. The Alumni of the departments maintain charitable fund with the
                                                aim
                                                of
                                                supporting the old students of the college. Alumni also insist on
                                                offering a
                                                cash prize for the UG and PG toppers of the Department. The Alumni
                                                association
                                                of the department provides scholarships, placement training, and various
                                                student
                                                support programs. Alumni sponsor books, uniforms and tuition fees to the
                                                economically backward students of the college.
                                                <br/>
                                                <br/>
                                                Alumni’s of each department follows the practice of collecting feedbacks
                                                and
                                                suggestions from each member where better conduct is assured in the
                                                coming
                                                years. Alumni of the college actively participate in curricular and
                                                co-curricular betterments of the institution. College alumni is having
                                                its
                                                overseas branches in the United Arab Emirates, Qatar, and the Kingdom of
                                                Saudi
                                                Arabia.
                                            </div>
                                        </div>
                                        <div class="col-md-3">
                                            <h2 style="padding:40px 0;text-align:center;font-size:20px;font-weight: 600;">
                                                Registration Certificate
                                            </h2>
                                            <div class="certificate">
                                                <img src="mes_college/static/img/alumni-certificate.jpg"
                                                     class="img-fluid"/>
                                            </div>
                                            <h2 style="padding:40px 0 10px;text-align:center;font-size:20px;font-weight: 600;">
                                                Reports
                                            </h2>
                                            <section class="naac_link" id="alumni_repo">
                                                <a href="/res-chemistry" class="readmore" id="naac_link">
                                                    Report Heading
                                                    <span class="fa fa-long-arrow-right text-o-color-3"
                                                          data-bs-original-title="" title=""
                                                          aria-describedby="tooltip544395"></span>
                                                </a>
                                            </section>
                                        </div>
                                    </div>
                                    <h2 class="main-head" style="text-align:left; padding-top:20px;">
                                        Alumni Activities
                                    </h2>
                                </div>
                            </section>
                        </div>
                    </t>
                </t>
            </field>
        </record>
        <record id="alumni_associates_page" model="website.page">
            <field name="url">/alumni_associate</field>
            <field name="is_published">True</field>
            <field name="view_id" ref="alumni_associates"/>
            <field name="track">True</field>
        </record>
    </data>
</odoo>