<odoo>
    <data>
        <record id="code_of_ethics" model="ir.ui.view">
            <field name="name">Code Of Ethics</field>
            <field name="type">qweb</field>
            <field name="key">emea_college_theme.code_of_ethics</field>
            <field name="arch" type="xml">
                <t name="job-1" t-name="emea_college_theme.code_of_ethics_menu">
                    <t t-call="website.layout">
                        <div id="wrap" class="oe_structure">
                            <section class=" page">
                                <h2 class="page_head">Code of Ethics</h2>
                                <div class="page_text">

                                    The college has directed research guides, Research scholars and the system of
                                    assessment of academic and research work leading to award of degrees at Masters and
                                    Research level in the form of thesis, dissertation and research publications, books
                                    and chapters in books and similar research works which reflected the highest element
                                    of academic integrity and originality observed as per provision of the college and
                                    University Grants Commission (UGC).
                                    <br/>

                                    A research committee is formed to monitor and promote the research activities among
                                    students and teachers on the campus. It gives advice and assist to the Head of the
                                    institution and the College Council in the fulfillment of the research aspects of
                                    the College Strategic Plan. The mission of the research committee is to enhance
                                    quality research by adhering to the highest ethical standards and professional best
                                    practices and to inculcate innovation and performance centered research culture
                                    among faculties and students. To minimize the plagiarism in research works, College
                                    Central library has started the Plagiarism Checking Service using the software
                                    URKUND provided by the University of Calicut.
                                </div>
                            </section>
                        </div>
                    </t>
                </t>
            </field>
        </record>
        <record id="code_of_ethics_page" model="website.page">
            <field name="url">/code_of_ethics</field>
            <field name="is_published">True</field>
            <field name="view_id" ref="code_of_ethics"/>
            <field name="track">True</field>
        </record>
    </data>
</odoo>