<odoo>
    <data>
        <record id="ipr_cell" model="ir.ui.view">
            <field name="name">IPR Cell</field>
            <field name="type">qweb</field>
            <field name="key">mes_college.ipr_cell</field>
            <field name="arch" type="xml">
                <t name="english" t-name="mes_college.ipr_cell_menu">
                    <t t-call="website.layout">
                        <div id="wrap" class="oe_structure">
                            <section class="bg_color">
                                <div class="container" id="container_width">
                                    <div class="row">
                                        <div class=" pt32 pb32 col-md-9">
                                            <div>
                                                <h2 class="main-head" style="text-align:left; padding-top:20px;">
                                                    IPR Cell
                                                </h2>
                                                <div class="content_text" style="text-align:justify;padding: 0;">
                                                    Intellectual property plays an important role in providing a
                                                    competitive edge to any Institution. The tangible assets like
                                                    inventions, designs, software, brand name and other creative &amp;
                                                    innovative ideas are more valuable than physical assets. MES Kalladi
                                                    College IPR Cell is committed to encourage, protect, manage and
                                                    commercialize Intellectual Property such as Patent, Copyright,
                                                    Trademark etc. generated through the College. The cell creates
                                                    conducive environment in the academics for the development of
                                                    Intellectual Property. Faculty and students of MES Kalladi College
                                                    are actively participating in the IPR filing process in different
                                                    disciplines of Engineering &amp; Technology.
                                                    <br/>
                                                    <strong>
                                                        Importance of IPR
                                                    </strong>
                                                    <br/>
                                                    <br/>
                                                    It is necessary to protect the Intellectual property in order to
                                                    enable organizations to earn recognition or financial benefits.
                                                    Governments of various countries protect the innovative ideas of
                                                    the inventors through Intellectual Property Rights (IPR).
                                                    Recently, IPR has become a central issue in the developed and
                                                    developing countries. The rationale for this IPR lies in the
                                                    need to create awareness about the importance of IPRs as a
                                                    marketable financial asset and economic tool among the
                                                    researchers, faculty and students of the College. Intellectual
                                                    property Rights: means the rights derived from the IP e.g.
                                                    Patents, registered designs, copyright etc.Indian Government has
                                                    revised the National IPR Policy in May 2016 and its vision,
                                                    Mission and objectives are given as follows.
                                                    <br/>
                                                    <br/>
                                                    <strong>Types of IP:
                                                    </strong>
                                                    <br/>
                                                    <br/>
                                                    The intellectual properties can be broadly listed as follows:
                                                    <br/>
                                                    <ul>
                                                        <li>
                                                            Patent: is an exclusive right granted for an invention,
                                                            which is a product or a process that provides a new way of
                                                            doing something, or offers a new technical solution to a
                                                            problem.
                                                        </li>
                                                        <li>
                                                            Copyright: is an exclusive right given to the author of the
                                                            original literary, architectural, dramatic, musical and
                                                            artistic works; cinematograph films; and sound recordings.
                                                        </li>
                                                        <li>
                                                            Trade/Service mark: means a mark capable of being
                                                            represented graphically and which is capable of
                                                            distinguishing the goods or services of one person from
                                                            those of others and may include shape of goods, their
                                                            packaging and combination of colours.
                                                        </li>
                                                        <li>
                                                            Industrial Design: means only the features of shape,
                                                            configuration, pattern, ornament or composition of lines or
                                                            colours applied to any article whether in two dimensional or
                                                            three dimensional or in both forms, by any industrial
                                                            process or means, whether manual, mechanical or chemical,
                                                            separate or combined, which in the finished article appeal
                                                            to and are judged solely by the eye; but does not include
                                                            any mode or principle of construction or anything which is
                                                            in substance a mere mechanical device.
                                                        </li>
                                                        <li>
                                                            IC Layout Designs: means a layout of transistors and other
                                                            circuitry elements and includes lead wires connecting such
                                                            elements and expressed in any manner in a semiconductor
                                                            integrated circuit.
                                                        </li>
                                                        <li>
                                                            New Plant Variety: a plant variety that is novel, distinct
                                                            and shows uniform and stable characteristics.g)
                                                            Biotechnology Inventions: include recombinant products such
                                                            as vectors, nucleotide sequences and micro‐organisms.

                                                        </li>
                                                        <li>
                                                            Traditional Knowledge: The knowledge developed by the
                                                            indigenous or local communities for the use of a natural
                                                            resource with respect to agriculture, food, medicine etc.
                                                            over a period of time and has been passed from one
                                                            generation to another traditionally.
                                                        </li>
                                                        <li>
                                                            Geographical Indications: means an indication which identify
                                                            such goods as agricultural goods, natural goods as
                                                            originating or manufactured in the territory of a country or
                                                            manufactured in the territory of a country or a region or
                                                            locality in that territory where a given quality, reputation
                                                            or other characteristic of such goods is essentially
                                                            attributable to its geographical origin and in case where
                                                            such goods are manufactured one of the activities of either
                                                            the production or of processing or preparation of the goods
                                                            concerned takes place in such territory, regions or locality
                                                            as the case may be.
                                                        </li>
                                                        <li>
                                                            Sajna P (Department of Chemistry)-Coordinator
                                                        </li>
                                                    </ul>
                                                </div>
                                            </div>
                                        </div>
                                        <div class="col-md-3">
                                            <section class="naac_link">
                                                <a href="/code_of_ethics" class="readmore" id="naac_link">
                                                    Code Of Ethics
                                                    <span class="fa fa-long-arrow-right text-o-color-3"
                                                          data-bs-original-title=""
                                                          title="" aria-describedby="tooltip544395"></span>
                                                </a>
                                                <a href="/research-projects"
                                                   class="readmore" id="naac_link" target="_blank">
                                                    Research Projects

                                                    <span class="fa fa-long-arrow-right text-o-color-3"
                                                          data-bs-original-title=""
                                                          title="" aria-describedby="tooltip544395"></span>
                                                </a>
                                                <a href="/research-promotion-council" class="readmore" id="naac_link">
                                                    Research Promotion Council
                                                    <span class="fa fa-long-arrow-right text-o-color-3"
                                                          data-bs-original-title=""
                                                          title="" aria-describedby="tooltip544395"></span>
                                                </a>
                                                <a href="#" class="readmore" id="naac_link">Research Facilities
                                                    <span class="fa fa-long-arrow-right text-o-color-3"
                                                          data-bs-original-title=""
                                                          title="" aria-describedby="tooltip544395"></span>
                                                </a>
                                                <a href="#" class="readmore" id="naac_link">Research Guides
                                                    <span class="fa fa-long-arrow-right text-o-color-3"
                                                          data-bs-original-title=""
                                                          title="" aria-describedby="tooltip544395"></span>
                                                </a>
                                            </section>
                                        </div>
                                    </div>
                                </div>
                            </section>
                        </div>
                    </t>
                </t>
            </field>
        </record>
        <record id="ipr_cell_page" model="website.page">
            <field name="url">/ipr_cell</field>
            <field name="is_published">True</field>
            <field name="view_id" ref="ipr_cell"/>
            <field name="track">True</field>
        </record>
    </data>
</odoo>