<odoo>
    <data>
        <record id="capability_enhancement" model="ir.ui.view">
            <field name="name">Capability Enhancement</field>
            <field name="type">qweb</field>
            <field name="key">emea_college_theme.capability_enhancement</field>
            <field name="arch" type="xml">
                <t name="Capability Enhancement" t-name="emea_college_theme.capability_menu">
                    <t t-call="website.layout">
                        <div id="wrap" class="oe_structure">
                            <section class=" page">
                                <h2 class="page_head">Capability Enhancement and Development Schemes</h2>
                                <div class="page_text">
                                    <h3 class="sub_head">GUIDANCE FOR COMPETITIVE EXAMINATIONS</h3>
                                    The College has initiated various competitive examinations to improve the capability
                                    of students who are ready and interested to prepare for competitive examinations.
                                    The centre is providing regular coaching for UGC-NET, Kerala PSC, UPSC, and Bank
                                    Tests. The guidance courses offered by the college help the students prepare
                                    thoroughly for the competitive exams. The syllabi of such courses stick on to the
                                    point of view from which the competitive exams are held. The basic categories of
                                    questions that are asked for such exams are explained and taught in length. These
                                    courses help to an overall development of language and other subject wise skills to
                                    the students.
                                    <br/>
                                    <br/>

                                    <h3 class="sub_head">CAREER COUNSELLING</h3>
                                    The College has a career counseling cell. The main aim of Career Counseling is to
                                    help the students to choose a field that is in tune with their skills and their job
                                    expectations. With the help of career counseling, most students end up choosing the
                                    right career and perform their level best, which ultimately helps them succeed.
                                    Career Counseling helps the students to understand their strength and weakness. It
                                    helps them to work on their short comings and prepares them to face interviews.
                                    These sessions make sure the students are well prepared to face the outside world
                                    and help them to understand the work culture of the companies. Placement cell
                                    organizes career counseling sessions for all the students especially final years on
                                    regular intervals
                                    <br/>
                                    <br/>

                                    <h3 class="sub_head">SOFTSKILL DEVELOPMENT</h3>
                                    Soft Skill development is an essential thing in the current growing world. The
                                    students at the college are taught to communicate and interact at a professional
                                    level. The qualities of confidence and critical thinking are developed making the
                                    students better at soft skills. Soft skill development courses inculcate ethical
                                    attitude towards others and also help in the nurturing of better interpersonal
                                    skills. Much of the communication related activities are developed and taught to
                                    students who are willing and interested to enhance their skills.
                                    <br/>
                                    <br/>

                                    <h3 class="sub_head">REMEDIAL COACHING</h3>
                                    College is providing regular remedial coaching to the slow learners. Remedial
                                    coaching is undertaken by individual lecturers of each department to provide some
                                    extra academic help to slow learners and those students who have been observed to
                                    score consistently low marks in the internal examinations. These students are
                                    re-taught parts of the syllabus that they could not follow in the classes. Certain
                                    additional assignments and tests are administered to them to ascertain their
                                    progress in learning the concepts that they could not master during the class
                                    lectures and continuous internal assessments. These classes are generally held in
                                    the sixth hour. Students lacking in confidence to ask questions during class hours
                                    also benefit from these classes as they are able to put forth their queries freely
                                    in smaller groups. An important skill that students with poor writing skills learn
                                    during these classes is the art of organizing the points in an essay-type answer as
                                    per the requirements of the question. Remedial coaching has been shown to improve
                                    the performance of those students who struggle to keep up with the demands of the
                                    syllabus in the semester system
                                    <br/>
                                    <br/>

                                    <h3 class="sub_head">BRIDGE COURSE</h3>
                                    Bridge course is offered by all the Departments to First year students to connect
                                    them to the UG Syllabus. The course also aims at aiding the students in learning to
                                    listen to lectures in English effectively and comprehend them properly, speaking
                                    fluently so as to be able to express the basic concepts. Students coming from rural
                                    backgrounds and those who face minor challenges with language are particularly able
                                    to benefit from this course.
                                    <br/>
                                    <br/>

                                    <h3 class="sub_head">PERSONAL COUNSELLING</h3>
                                    Personal counseling sessions are undertaken by the professional counselor appointed
                                    by the college and the trained teachers of our college. The counselor helps students
                                    with problems during their stay in the college. Counseling is a collaborative effort
                                    between the counselor and the client. This kind of collaboration helps the clients
                                    identify goals and potential solutions to the problems which cause emotional
                                    turmoil, seek to improve communication and coping skills, strength self-esteem and
                                    promote behavior change and optimal mental health. The counselor serves as an
                                    empathetic listener. The counselor analyses the problems of the students and takes a
                                    standardized psychological method to treat the student. The students might face
                                    emotional turbulence due to various problems like depression, abuse, harassment,
                                    family problems etc… The counselor provides guidance and advice on solving the
                                    problems through the counseling sessions. The information shared by the students
                                    during the personal counseling sessions is kept confidential and dealt with
                                    compassionately. The Counseling Cell of the college takes care of all the counseling
                                    related activities. They make up the core body that deals with issues faced by the
                                    students and provide early interventions, help and support to them.
                                    <br/>
                                    <br/>

                                    <h3 class="sub_head">YOGA AND MEDITATION</h3>
                                    Since teaching and learning demands more concentration our college gives more
                                    emphasis for Yoga and meditation. Yoga is defined as a physical, mental and
                                    spiritual practice which has its roots in ancient India. Yoga is practiced widely
                                    around the world for around thousand years and has developed various
                                    interpretations. Yoga mainly is stretching exercises to build flexibility and relax
                                    the body and mind. The college has initiated to conduct yoga and meditation to
                                    encourage students for living a healthy and balanced life. The yoga classes have
                                    been helpful and supportive to the students. Meditation classes have helped the
                                    students use techniques of mindfulness and train their mental ability to concentrate
                                    their attention on a particular subject or thought.
                                    <br/>
                                    <br/>

                                    <h3 class="sub_head">LANGUAGE LAB</h3>
                                    Good communication skills are indispensable for the success of any professional. If
                                    one wants to reach out to people, he or she has to speak their language. The English
                                    language, in particular, has become essential in the lives of young people who
                                    aspire to advance their careers anywhere in the world. English language learning has
                                    therefore become a must for any Indian student today. This programme enhances
                                    linguistic skills while improving communication, with an emphasis on phonetics for
                                    language fluency. It encourages sound listening and speaking abilities. Reading
                                    comprehension makes sure students utilize their analytical and interpretive
                                    abilities. Practical exercises provide ample opportunities to practice language and
                                    grammar skills. The demonstration of sentence formation provides clarity of usage of
                                    grammatical elements.
                                </div>
                            </section>
                            <h3 class="in_charge">In-Charge
                            </h3>
                            <div class="row">
                                <section class="former_card"  >
                                    <img src="/emea_college_theme/static/img/alumni4.jpg"
                                         alt="Person"
                                         class="card-image"/>
                                    <div class="card-content">
                                        <div class="name">Name Of Professor</div>
                                        <div class="designation">Designation Of Professor
                                            <br/>
                                        </div>
                                    </div>
                                </section>
                            </div>
                            <section class="pb32" style="text-align:center;">
                                <h2 class="page_head pt32">REPORTS</h2>
                                <a href="#" target="_blank" title="Download"
                                   data-target="tooltip"
                                   class="readmore" id="readmore">
                                    Report 2014-23
                                </a>
                            </section>
                        </div>
                    </t>
                </t>
            </field>
        </record>
        <record id="capability_enhancement_page" model="website.page">
            <field name="url">/capability_enhancement</field>
            <field name="is_published">True</field>
            <field name="view_id" ref="capability_enhancement"/>
            <field name="track">True</field>
        </record>
    </data>
</odoo>