<odoo>
    <data>
        <record id="admission_procedure" model="ir.ui.view">
            <field name="name">admission_procedure</field>
            <field name="type">qweb</field>
            <field name="key">mes_college.admission_procedure</field>
            <field name="arch" type="xml">
                <t name="english" t-name="mes_college.admission_procedure_menu">
                    <t t-call="website.layout">
                        <div id="wrap" class="oe_structure">
                            <div id="wrap" class="oe_structure">
                                <section class="bg_color">
                                    <div class="container" id="container_width">
                                        <div class="row">
                                            <div class=" pt32 pb32 col-md-8">
                                                <div>
                                                    <h2 class="main-head" style="text-align:left">Admission Procedure
                                                    </h2>
                                                    <div class="content_text" style="text-align:left;padding: 0;">
                                                        <strong>
                                                            CENTRALIZED ADMISSION PROCESS (CAP)
                                                        </strong>
                                                        <br/>
                                                        <br/>
                                                        <strong style="font-size:12px;">Introduction</strong>
                                                        <br/>
                                                        <br/>
                                                        Admission to merit seats in the /programmes/courses in Arts and
                                                        Science colleges affiliated to the University of Calicut
                                                        (including
                                                        50% of seats set apart for Merit Admission in the Self Financing
                                                        colleges and Self Financing programmes/ courses in Aided
                                                        colleges)
                                                        are being conducted through Centralized Admission Process (CAP).
                                                        <br/>
                                                        <br/>
                                                        <strong style="font-size:12px;">Aims and Objectives:</strong>
                                                        <br/>
                                                        <br/>
                                                        The University introduced the ‘Online registration’ for
                                                        admissions
                                                        to UG/PG programmes/courses in the academic year 2013-2014 to
                                                        cater
                                                        to the aspirations of students who otherwise could not pursue
                                                        tendering applications, by personally approaching various
                                                        Colleges
                                                        spread over 5 districts affiliated to the University for
                                                        admissions.
                                                        While introducing the Online Registration for Centralised
                                                        admission
                                                        the University aimed a lofty goal of extending a hand out to the
                                                        candidates from the socially backward sector of the society and
                                                        those residing in the remote areas within the jurisdiction of
                                                        Calicut University.
                                                        <br/>
                                                        <br/>
                                                        <strong style="font-size:12px;">Seat Nomenclature:</strong>
                                                        <br/>
                                                        <br/>
                                                        The seats available in the various colleges are classified as
                                                        <ol>
                                                            <li>Merit</li>
                                                            <li>Mandatory reservations</li>
                                                            <li>Community</li>
                                                            <li>Management</li>
                                                            <li>Other Reservation Category Seats</li>
                                                            <li>Special Reservation Category seats.</li>
                                                        </ol>
                                                        <strong style="font-size:12px;">Admission Schedule/Notification
                                                        </strong>
                                                        The admission schedule will be prepared and published in the
                                                        admission notification every year. The date of commencement of
                                                        online registration to the closing date of admissions will be
                                                        available in the admission schedule. The dates for each
                                                        allotment
                                                        and admissions to all categories will be published in the
                                                        admission
                                                        schedule.
                                                        <br/>
                                                        <br/>
                                                        <strong style="font-size:12px;">Mandatory Fee.
                                                        </strong>
                                                        <br/>
                                                        <br/>
                                                        The candidates receiving allotment should remit the Mandatory
                                                        Fee
                                                        prescribed in the admission notification. The mandatory fee need
                                                        to
                                                        be remitted only once. The candidates failing to remit mandatory
                                                        fee
                                                        will lose his/her current allotment and they will be expelled
                                                        from
                                                        further allotments. The candidates, thus expelled will not be
                                                        reinstated in the allotment process at any stage of the
                                                        allotment.
                                                        <br/>
                                                        <br/>
                                                        The candidates admitted other than through allotment should also
                                                        compulsorily remit mandatory fee.
                                                        <br/>
                                                        <br/>
                                                        <strong style="font-size:12px;">Eligibility for Admission
                                                        </strong>
                                                        <br/>
                                                        <br/>
                                                        Those candidates who are “Eligible for Higher Studies” as per
                                                        the
                                                        Kerala State Higher Secondary Examination or a pass in the
                                                        equivalent examinations are the minimum criteria for admission
                                                        to
                                                        degree courses, unless otherwise specified.
                                                        However, candidates who have qualified the HSE and VHSE of the
                                                        Government of Kerala under ‘SAY’ scheme and Compartmental
                                                        Examination of CBSE are also eligible for admission to first
                                                        year
                                                        degree programmes/courses in the same academic year.
                                                        Candidates who have passed the Higher Secondary Examination of
                                                        Tamil
                                                        Nadu (Private study) will not be admitted to any course under
                                                        this
                                                        University. (U.ONo.GAI/ A1/5062/2002 dated 07.07.2005).
                                                        Eligibility of each PG Programme is specified based on the
                                                        eligible
                                                        UG programmes and the % marks obtained in different Parts.
                                                        Relaxation in the requirement of minimum marks upto 5% for OBC
                                                        /OEC
                                                        is applicable. SC/ST candidates need a pass only in their
                                                        qualifying
                                                        examination for admission to the Post Graduate Programmes.
                                                        Detailed eligibility and indexing rules for various
                                                        courses/programmes will be published in the prospectus.
                                                        <br/>
                                                        <br/>
                                                        <strong style="font-size:12px;">Nodal Centres
                                                        </strong>
                                                        <br/>
                                                        <br/>
                                                        Nodal Centres are functioning in all affiliated colleges in
                                                        connection with the admission to function as a helping hand to
                                                        the
                                                        students and University. The students can do registration,
                                                        editing,
                                                        re arrangement of option, cancellation of higher option etc
                                                        through
                                                        the Nodal Centres. The students can also utilise the Nodal
                                                        Centres
                                                        for clearing their doubts and clarification regarding the
                                                        Centralised Admission process (CAP).<br/>The list of Nodal
                                                        Centres
                                                        is published in the website.(www.cuonline.ac.in)
                                                        <br/>
                                                        <br/>
                                                        <strong style="font-size:16px;">Instructions for Applying
                                                            through
                                                            CAP. Visit the website
                                                            <a href="www.cuonline.ac.in">www.cuonline.ac.in</a>
                                                        </strong>
                                                        <br/>
                                                        <br/>
                                                        The admission through Centralised Admission process to First
                                                        year
                                                        Degree/P.G/Afsal-ul-ulama preliminary/B.Ed/ M.Ed/and Programmes
                                                        with
                                                        Entrance Examination will be conducted in TWO phases.
                                                        <br/>
                                                        The registration will be conducted in Two continuous Phases.
                                                        <br/>
                                                        Phase 1: Fee Payment.
                                                        <br/>
                                                        Phase 2: Submission of Application :
                                                        <br/>
                                                        <strong style="font-size:12px;">
                                                            Phase 1: Keep ready the following:
                                                        </strong>
                                                        <br/>
                                                        <br/>
                                                        <ol type="a">
                                                            <li>
                                                                Date of Birth: copy of S.S.L.C
                                                            </li>
                                                            <li>Mobile Number: mobile number of student/parents/
                                                                guardian only to be furnished. Vital informations
                                                                regarding
                                                                the allotment and admissions are being communicated
                                                                through
                                                                SMS to the registered mobile number. Therefore, under
                                                                any
                                                                circumstance the mobile number of Akshaya centres,
                                                                internet
                                                                cafe or other agencies should not be submitted.
                                                            </li>
                                                            <li>E-mail: Email Id of student/parents/guardian only be
                                                                entered. Those who do not have an Email-Id may create
                                                                one
                                                                and enter. Vital informations regarding the allotment
                                                                and
                                                                admissions will also be communicated through Email to
                                                                the
                                                                registered mail id
                                                            </li>
                                                            <li>Application Fee : As per admission notification for each
                                                                Course/Programme.
                                                            </li>
                                                        </ol>
                                                        <br/>
                                                        <br/>
                                                        <strong style="font-size:12px;">Instructions for Payment of Fee
                                                            (through e-payment system)
                                                        </strong>
                                                        <br/>
                                                        <ol>
                                                            <li>
                                                                Visit the website
                                                                <a href="https://www.uoc.ac.in">https://www.uoc.ac.in
                                                                </a>
                                                            </li>
                                                            <li>
                                                                Click Instant Pay- Select Purpose of payment
                                                            </li>
                                                            <li>Furnish the details required. (Mobile number and e-mail
                                                                id of student/parent/guardian only to be furnished)
                                                            </li>
                                                            <li>Select mode of payment</li>
                                                        </ol>
                                                        <br/>
                                                        <br/>
                                                        <strong style="font-size:12px;">
                                                            Mode of Remittance of fee by candidates from inside KERALA
                                                        </strong>
                                                        <br/>
                                                        <br/>
                                                        <ol type="a">
                                                            <li>
                                                                State Bank online payment. (For those who have State
                                                                Bank
                                                                online banking facility).
                                                            </li>
                                                            <li>
                                                                Payment Gateway
                                                            </li>
                                                            <li>
                                                                Nodal Centres (Functioning in All Colleges) List of
                                                                Nodal Centres is available in www.cuonline.ac.in)
                                                            </li>
                                                            <li>Akshaya Centres
                                                            </li>
                                                            <li>Friends JanasevanaKendram
                                                            </li>
                                                            <li>Other firms providing Internet Facility</li>
                                                        </ol>
                                                        <br/>
                                                        <br/>
                                                        <strong style="font-size:12px;">Remit the fee in any of the mode
                                                            of
                                                            payment mentioned above.
                                                        </strong>
                                                        <br/>
                                                        <br/>
                                                        <ol type="a">
                                                            <li>
                                                                After remitting fee in any of the mode mentioned above
                                                                the
                                                                CAP ID and password will be received in the registered
                                                                mobile number through SMS.
                                                            </li>
                                                            <li>For the programmes/courses with entrance examination,
                                                                the
                                                                chalan number and password will be received in the
                                                                registered mobile number through SMS.
                                                                After receiving the SMS online application can be
                                                                submitted
                                                            </li>
                                                        </ol>
                                                        <br/>
                                                        <br/>
                                                        <strong style="font-size:12px;">
                                                            Mode of online payment
                                                        </strong>
                                                        <br/>
                                                        <br/>
                                                        <ol>
                                                            <li>Select the Purpose of remittance.</li>
                                                            <li>Furnish the details in the blank fields (mobile number
                                                                and
                                                                e-mail ID only that of the student/parent/guardian).
                                                            </li>
                                                            <li>Select the mode of payment</li>
                                                            <li>Enter the fee amount and click the button”Proceed”.</li>
                                                            <li>You can view the details now, if the details are correct
                                                                click “ Pay Now.”
                                                            </li>
                                                            <li>In the next page click “Continue for Payment”.Remit the
                                                                fee
                                                                online as per the instructions in the online payment
                                                                site of
                                                                the
                                                                Bank selected.
                                                            </li>
                                                            <li>Click redirect to the Calicut University Instant Web
                                                                Payment
                                                                System (CUIWPS) or wait for 60 seconds to be redirected.
                                                            </li>
                                                            <li>Take printout of the online payment “RECEIPT”. CAP ID
                                                                Number
                                                                and Password will be received by SMS/e-mail, with which
                                                                the
                                                                candidate can login to CAP and complete the online
                                                                application
                                                                submission.
                                                            </li>
                                                        </ol>
                                                        <br/>
                                                        <br/>
                                                        <strong>The payment procedure completed.”
                                                            <br/>
                                                            Fee once remitted will not be refunded”
                                                            <br/>
                                                            PHASE 2: Keep ready the following for the submission of
                                                            application for UG/PG/Afsal-ul-ulama preliminary/B.Ed/ M.Ed
                                                            Keep
                                                            ready the following
                                                        </strong>
                                                        <br/>
                                                        <br/>
                                                        <ol>
                                                            <li>
                                                                The CAP ID/Chalan number and password received by SMS/
                                                                E-Mail.
                                                            </li>
                                                            <li>Copy of the Qualifying Examination Mark Sheet.
                                                            </li>
                                                            <li>
                                                                Passport size photograph in ‘.jpg’ format with a size
                                                                between 20KB and 40 KB.
                                                            </li>
                                                            <li>
                                                                Prepare the list of colleges/courses according to the
                                                                applicants priority. The fee structure for the self
                                                                financing programmes will be different from the fee
                                                                structure of Government/Aided programme.List of colleges
                                                                and
                                                                programmes/courses are available in the
                                                                website.(www.cuonline.ac.in). The fee structure for each
                                                                year will be published along with the admission
                                                                prospectus.
                                                            </li>
                                                            <li>BPL Certificate for candidates belongs to BPL category
                                                                among forward communities.
                                                            </li>
                                                        </ol>
                                                        <br/>
                                                        <br/>
                                                        <strong style="font-size:12px;">
                                                            Instructions for submission of application for
                                                            UG/PG/Afsal-ululama preliminary/B.Ed/M.Ed.
                                                            <br/>
                                                            Visit www.cuonline.ac.in-Select UG/PG Registration-Login
                                                            with
                                                            CAP ID, registration number and password.
                                                        </strong>
                                                        <br/>
                                                        <br/>
                                                        The application submission is done in Four Parts.
                                                        <br>
                                                        </br>
                                                        <strong style="font-size:12px;">
                                                            Part1: Photo Upload ( Passport size photograph in ‘.jpg’
                                                            formatwith a size between 20KB and 40 KB
                                                        </strong>
                                                        <br/>
                                                        <br/>
                                                        <strong style="font-size:12px;">
                                                            Part 2: Student Profile
                                                        </strong>
                                                        <br/>
                                                        <br/>
                                                        <ol>
                                                            <li>
                                                                Basic Details
                                                                <br/>
                                                                Enter the details in the blank fields.
                                                                <br/>
                                                                b. Personal Details:
                                                                <br/>
                                                                1. Utmost care should be taken while entering
                                                                reservation
                                                                details. Opt only the eligible reservations otherwise
                                                                admission will be denied.
                                                                <br/>
                                                                2. Those who apply for the seats reserved for BPL
                                                                category
                                                                among forward communities should submit the order No,
                                                                date
                                                                of order and details of issuing authority.
                                                                <br/>
                                                                3. Weightage: Enter the eligible bonus/weightage if any.
                                                                The details entered can be edited. To move to the next
                                                                part
                                                                CLICK “SAVE /PROCEED” BUTTON.
                                                                <br/>
                                                            </li>
                                                        </ol>
                                                        <br/>
                                                        <strong style="font-size:12px;">
                                                            Part 3: Qualification Details
                                                        </strong>
                                                        <br/>
                                                        <ol>
                                                            <li>
                                                                Enter number of chances taken to pass the qualifying
                                                                examinations. 10 marks will be reduced for each
                                                                additional
                                                                chances
                                                                taken to pass the qualifying examination subject to a
                                                                maximum of 25
                                                                marks.
                                                            </li>
                                                            <li>Specify the Board/University of the qualifying
                                                                examinations.
                                                            </li>
                                                            <li>Enter the stream of study of the Qualifying
                                                                examinations,
                                                                if
                                                                necessary (Science, Humanities, Commerce).
                                                            </li>
                                                            <li>
                                                                Verify the marks displayed automatically; otherwise
                                                                enter
                                                                the
                                                                marks.
                                                            </li>
                                                            <li>Utmost care should be taken while entering the marks.
                                                                The details entered can be edited. To move to the next
                                                                part
                                                                CLICK
                                                                “SAVE /PROCEED” BUTTON
                                                            </li>
                                                        </ol>
                                                        <br/>
                                                        <strong style="font-size:12px;">Part 4: College Course Selection
                                                        </strong>
                                                        <br/>
                                                        <br/>
                                                        <b>(Utmost care should be taken while fixing the priority of the
                                                            option. Priority and index marks are the base of the
                                                            allotment)
                                                        </b>
                                                        <br/>
                                                        <br/>
                                                        Furnish the details of colleges and programmes/courses according
                                                        to
                                                        the priority. The candidates who wish to apply for the community
                                                        quota in Aided colleges can opt the colleges and
                                                        programmes/courses
                                                        according to the priority.
                                                        Candidates can view the options submitted and if necessary can
                                                        edit
                                                        the options. The candidates can take a verification print out to
                                                        verify and ensure that the details submitted are correct. If the
                                                        details entered are correct click “Final Submit”.
                                                        After final submission the candidates can take a final “Print
                                                        Out” (
                                                        College copy and Student Copy). The student copy shall be
                                                        retained
                                                        and the college copy shall be submitted to the college where
                                                        he/she
                                                        takes permanent admission.
                                                        <br/>
                                                        <strong style="font-size:12px;">Cancellation of higher options.
                                                        </strong>
                                                        Cancellation of all the higher options can only be done through
                                                        Nodal Centres. Partial cancellation of the higher options can be
                                                        done by the candidates themselves or can use the services of the
                                                        Akshaya Centres and other firms providing internet facility.
                                                        <br/>
                                                        <br/>
                                                        The candidates can login into CAP with their login credentials
                                                        after
                                                        each allotment for partial cancellation.
                                                        <br/>
                                                        <strong style="font-size:12px;">Rearrangement of college and
                                                            course
                                                        </strong>
                                                        After the trial allotment the candidates can rearrange priority
                                                        of
                                                        their options already submitted during the registration by “drag
                                                        and
                                                        drop” facility. No new course or college can be added at any
                                                        stage
                                                        of the allotment process.
                                                        <br/>
                                                        <br/>
                                                        <strong style="font-size:12px;">Allotment
                                                        </strong>
                                                        <br/>
                                                        <br/>
                                                        There will be Three allotments for all category of students and
                                                        Two
                                                        special allotment for SC/ST/BPL in forward caste. On receipt of
                                                        the
                                                        allotment to an option, all the options below the received
                                                        allotment
                                                        will be permanently lost. The options thus lost will not be
                                                        reinstated at any cost.
                                                        <br/>
                                                        <strong style="font-size:12px;">Permanent Admissions
                                                        </strong>
                                                        The candidates receiving allotments for the first options and
                                                        those
                                                        candidates are satisfied with the allotment received in any of
                                                        the
                                                        allotment can take permenant admissions to the respective
                                                        colleges.
                                                        After Fourth allotment all candidates should take Permenant
                                                        admissions to the colleges allotted.
                                                        <br/>
                                                        <br/>
                                                        In case the higher options are not cancelled the candidate will
                                                        be
                                                        considered for the higher options and will be bound to
                                                        relinquish
                                                        the previous allotment and must take admission to the allotment
                                                        received to their higher options.
                                                        <br/>
                                                        <br/>
                                                        Temporary Admissions
                                                        <br/>
                                                        <br/>
                                                        After third allotment all candidates who have received allotment
                                                        but
                                                        not satisfied with their current allotment and willing to be
                                                        considered for higher option shall take Temporary Admission.
                                                        These
                                                        candidates will be considered for their higher options.
                                                        <br/>
                                                        <br/>
                                                        The candidates taking temporary admissions need not remit any
                                                        fee or
                                                        submit any certificates to the college. But, the form provided
                                                        in
                                                        annexure 1 shall be submitted to the college.

                                                    </div>
                                                </div>
                                            </div>
                                            <div class="col-md-4">
                                                <h2 class="main-head">Admission Cell</h2>
                                                <div class="col-md-7 mb32 mx-auto" >
                                                    <div class="faculties">
                                                        <div class="faculty_img">
                                                            <img src="/mes_college/static/img/faculty.jpg"
                                                                 class="w-100 h-100"/>
                                                        </div>
                                                        <div class="faculty_name">
                                                            Dr. Zainul Abid T
                                                        </div>
                                                        <div class="designation">Nodal Officer-UG Admission</div>
                                                    </div>
                                                </div>
                                                <div class="col-md-7 mb32 mx-auto">
                                                    <div class="faculties">
                                                        <div class="faculty_img">
                                                            <img src="/mes_college/static/img/faculty.jpg"
                                                                 class="w-100 h-100"/>
                                                        </div>
                                                        <div class="faculty_name">
                                                            Abdul Basid PK
                                                        </div>
                                                        <div class="designation">Nodal Officer-PG Admission</div>
                                                    </div>
                                                </div>
                                                <div class="col-md-7 mb32 mx-auto">
                                                    <div class="faculties">
                                                        <div class="faculty_img">
                                                            <img src="/mes_college/static/img/faculty.jpg"
                                                                 class="w-100 h-100"/>
                                                        </div>
                                                        <div class="faculty_name">
                                                            Ratheesh CK
                                                        </div>
                                                        <div class="designation">Assistant Nodal Officer</div>
                                                    </div>
                                                </div>
                                            </div>
                                        </div>
                                    </div>
                                </section>
                            </div>
                        </div>
                    </t>
                </t>
            </field>
        </record>
        <record id="admission_procedure_page" model="website.page">
            <field name="url">/admission_procedure</field>
            <field name="is_published">True</field>
            <field name="view_id" ref="admission_procedure"/>
            <field name="track">True</field>
        </record>
    </data>
</odoo>