<odoo>
    <data>
        <record id="counselling" model="ir.ui.view">
            <field name="name">Counselling</field>
            <field name="type">qweb</field>
            <field name="key">mes_college.counselling</field>
            <field name="arch" type="xml">
                <t name="english" t-name="mes_college.counselling_menu">
                    <t t-call="website.layout">
                        <div id="wrap" class="oe_structure">
                            <section class="bg_color">
                                <div class="container" id="container_width">
                                    <div class="row">
                                        <div class=" pt32 pb32 col-md-8">
                                            <div>
                                                <h2 class="main-head" style="text-align:left">Counselling</h2>
                                                <div class="text_content">
                                                    <strong>
                                                        General Counselling
                                                    </strong>
                                                    <br/>
                                                    <br/>
                                                    The general counseling center started in the College with the vision
                                                    of
                                                    addressing the needs and problems of Students community at their
                                                    intra
                                                    personal, interpersonal and social levels; and thereby increasing
                                                    their
                                                    mental health. The purpose of this Centre is to help students in
                                                    their
                                                    personal development. , and also help the students deal with day to
                                                    day
                                                    problems, issues, crises and other painful life events.
                                                    Some of the common issues faced by the students are problems in
                                                    studies
                                                    like lack of concentration, absents, exam fear, anxiety,
                                                    depressions,
                                                    suicidal intention, confusions, addictions of various types and
                                                    handling
                                                    relationships in personal and family life. The various activity of
                                                    the
                                                    centre like one to one counseling, group counseling, trainings and
                                                    seminars help the students to get awareness,learn coping skills and
                                                    makes their experiences as students to be more productive and
                                                    successful
                                                    <br/>
                                                    <br/>
                                                    <b>The mission of general counselling is</b>
                                                    <br/>
                                                    <ul>
                                                        <li>To promote mental health of students.
                                                        </li>
                                                        <li>Provide awareness classes to avoid alcoholism, drug abuse
                                                            and
                                                            marital disharmony
                                                        </li>
                                                        <li>Crisis intervention and proper management.</li>
                                                        <li>
                                                            Create a better learning environment.
                                                        </li>
                                                    </ul>
                                                    The activities of the Counselling Centre are coordinated by
                                                    Department
                                                    of Psychology. Government has appointed a counsellor under the
                                                    Jeevani
                                                    Project
                                                    <br/>
                                                    <br/>
                                                    <strong>Premarital Counselling
                                                    </strong>
                                                    <br/>
                                                    <br/>
                                                    Premarital Counseling Centre is an initiative of Directorate of
                                                    Minority
                                                    Welfare, Govt. of Kerala for the social and family upliftment of
                                                    minority youth. Centre provides counseling courses to youth,
                                                    preparing
                                                    for marriage. The centre organizes four day counseling courses,
                                                    including eight sessions related to various aspects of family life,
                                                    such
                                                    as social impact of family life, Husband- Wife relationship, Legal
                                                    aspects of marriage , conflict management, Healthy sexual life,
                                                    parenting and family budgeting etc. Students are also given chances
                                                    to
                                                    interact with family counselors, psychologists, advocates and other
                                                    counseling experts.
                                                </div>
                                            </div>
                                        </div>
                                        <div class="col-md-4">
                                            <h2 class="main-head">Coordinator</h2>
                                            <div class="col-md-7 mb32 mx-auto">
                                                <div class="faculties">
                                                    <div class="faculty_img">
                                                        <img src="/mes_college/static/img/faculty.jpg"
                                                             class="w-100 h-100"/>
                                                    </div>
                                                    <div class="faculty_name">
                                                        Shihab AM
                                                    </div>
                                                    <div class="designation">Department of Islamic History</div>
                                                </div>
                                            </div>

                                        </div>
                                    </div>
                                </div>
                            </section>
                        </div>
                    </t>
                </t>
            </field>
        </record>
        <record id="counselling_page" model="website.page">
            <field name="url">/counselling</field>
            <field name="is_published">True</field>
            <field name="view_id" ref="counselling"/>
            <field name="track">True</field>
        </record>
    </data>
</odoo>