<odoo>
    <data>
        <record id="pta" model="ir.ui.view">
            <field name="name">pta</field>
            <field name="type">qweb</field>
            <field name="key">mes_college.pta</field>
            <field name="arch" type="xml">
                <t name="english" t-name="mes_college.pta_menu">
                    <t t-call="website.layout">
                        <div id="wrap" class="oe_structure">
                            <section class="bg_color">
                                <div class="container" id="container_width">
                                    <div class="row">
                                        <div class=" pt32 pb32 col-md-8">
                                            <div>
                                                <h2 class="main-head" style="text-align:left">PTA</h2>
                                                <div class="text_content">
                                                    An active PTA has been functioning in the college since 1976. It
                                                    regularly provides financial aid to economically backward students.
                                                    It
                                                    also sponsors some funds to the college for its infra structural
                                                    development where there is no Govt. aid or it is insufficient. It
                                                    motivates students who excel in academic field by giving cash
                                                    awards. It
                                                    gives proper guidance to the college authorities in maintaining
                                                    discipline inside the campus.
                                                    <br/>
                                                    <br/>
                                                    The parents of each student who is admitted in the college shall
                                                    join the Association by paying a membership fee. All the teachers
                                                    will
                                                    be the members of the association.
                                                    <br/>
                                                    <br/>
                                                    Principal is the President of PTA, one of the Teaching Staff Member
                                                    is
                                                    the Secretary, and one of the Executive Member from Parents is the
                                                    Vice
                                                    President. The Present Vice President is Sayyid Fasal Pookoyya
                                                    Thangal.
                                                    <br/>
                                                    <br/>Parent Teachers Association is always active in the overall
                                                    development of the college. Last year also they contributed
                                                    generously
                                                    for various activities of the institution. . It monitors the
                                                    discipline
                                                    in the institution. We collect parents feedback regularly and
                                                    incorporate their suggestions in the decision making process.
                                                    Endowment
                                                    scholarships were given to students who have special achievement in
                                                    arts
                                                    and sports.
                                                    <br/>
                                                    <ul>
                                                        <li>Participation of students in the A zone festival.
                                                        </li>
                                                        <li>Special cash award to University Examination rank holders
                                                            <ul>
                                                                <li>
                                                                    I Rank Rs 1000 each
                                                                </li>
                                                                <li>II Rank Rs 750 each</li>
                                                                <li>III Rank Rs 600 each</li>
                                                            </ul>
                                                        </li>
                                                        <li>Cash award to top scorers in University P.G. final
                                                            examination.
                                                        </li>
                                                        <li>Cash award to top scorers in University Degree final
                                                            Examination.
                                                        </li>
                                                        <li>Cash award to top scorers of University II year Degree
                                                            Examination.
                                                        </li>
                                                        <li>Cash award to top scorers of Ist year University Degree
                                                            Examination.
                                                        </li>
                                                        <li>PTA award to University rank holders.
                                                        </li>
                                                        <li>Financial assistance to purchase sports equipments.
                                                        </li>
                                                        <li>Financial support to various activities of NSS and NCC.
                                                        </li>
                                                        <li>Financial support for the participation of students in
                                                            sports/arts competitions outside the campus.
                                                        </li>
                                                        Vidyanidhi Scholarship: This merit scholarship is launched by
                                                        PTA in
                                                        2023

                                                    </ul>
                                                </div>
                                            </div>
                                        </div>
                                        <div class="col-md-4">
                                            <strong style="font-size:13px;text-align:center;">Coordinator</strong>
                                            <div class="col-md-7 mt16 mx-auto">
                                                <div class="faculties">
                                                    <div class="faculty_img">
                                                        <img src="/mes_college/static/img/faculty.jpg"
                                                             class="w-100 h-100"/>
                                                    </div>
                                                    <div class="faculty_name">
                                                        A M Shihab
                                                    </div>
                                                    <div class="designation">Assistant Professor</div>
                                                </div>
                                            </div>

                                        </div>
                                    </div>

                                </div>
                            </section>
                        </div>
                    </t>
                </t>
            </field>
        </record>
        <record id="pta_page" model="website.page">
            <field name="url">/pta</field>
            <field name="is_published">True</field>
            <field name="view_id" ref="pta"/>
            <field name="track">True</field>
        </record>
    </data>
</odoo>