<odoo>
    <data>
        <record id="library" model="ir.ui.view">
            <field name="name">library</field>
            <field name="type">qweb</field>
            <field name="key">mes_college.library</field>
            <field name="arch" type="xml">
                <t name="english" t-name="mes_college.library_menu">
                    <t t-call="website.layout">
                        <div id="wrap" class="oe_structure">
                            <section class="bg_color">
                                <div class="container" id="container_width">
                                    <div class="row">
                                        <div class=" pt32 pb32 col-md-9">
                                            <div>
                                                <h2 class="main-head" style="text-align:left; padding-top:20px;">
                                                    Library
                                                </h2>
                                                <div class="content_text" style="text-align:left;padding: 0;">
                                                    The library of M.E.S Kalladi College started functioning in the very
                                                    first year of establishment in
                                                    1967, in the early years it housed in a room in the main block, in
                                                    1990 the
                                                    library own an individual building. Now the library has total plinth
                                                    area of
                                                    5700 square feet with centralized air condition. The library have a
                                                    collection of 40528 books,40 subject journals, 12 Magzines and 6
                                                    newspapers.
                                                    <br/>
                                                    <br/>

                                                    The college has more than 2500 students with 115 faculty members.
                                                    The
                                                    library fully automated with RFID Technology, All members of the
                                                    college
                                                    library provided a RFID Tagged ID cards. It is the very first
                                                    academic
                                                    library in the district and third in the state with these
                                                    facilities.
                                                    <br/>
                                                    <br/>

                                                    Through Institutional membership more than 6000+ e-journals and
                                                    31,35,000+
                                                    e-books can be accessed under the project entitled “National Library
                                                    and
                                                    Information Services Infrastructure for scholarly Content (N-LIST)”
                                                    of
                                                    INFLIBNET Centre, Ahemdabad.
                                                    <br/>
                                                    <br/>

                                                    E-learning area is equipped with 25 systems to access the
                                                    e-resources.
                                                    Knowledge resource centre has Wi-Fi connectivity which enables the
                                                    users to
                                                    use their own laptops within the library.
                                                    <br/>
                                                    <br/>
                                                    <strong>LIBRARY HOUR</strong>
                                                    <br/>
                                                    <br/>
                                                    Working Days 8.30 AM to 5.30 PM
                                                    <br/>
                                                    Saturday: 9.00 AM to 3.00 PM
                                                    <br/>
                                                    <br/>
                                                    <strong>Mission and Vision</strong>
                                                    <br/>
                                                    <br/>
                                                    Libraries are engaged in learning and discovery as essential
                                                    participants in the educational community. We develop, organize,
                                                    provide access to and preserve materials to meet the needs of
                                                    present and future generations of students and scholars.
                                                    <br/>
                                                    <br/>
                                                    The library will be the hub and academic town square of the college
                                                    by being an essential component of the academic and creative life of
                                                    the institution. We will excel in: collecting, preserving, and
                                                    providing access to the best scholarly and educational resources;
                                                    providing high quality, innovative services; and creating a
                                                    welcoming and comfortable physical environment. We will foster an
                                                    atmosphere that encourages diversity, excellence, and continued
                                                    growth in finding ways to surpass our own high standards.
                                                    <br/>
                                                    <br/>
                                                    <strong>Facilities and services</strong>
                                                    <br/>
                                                    <br/>
                                                    <ul>
                                                        <li>
                                                            <strong>KOHA ILM Software:</strong>
                                                            Latest version 18.11
                                                        </li>
                                                        <li>
                                                            <strong>RFID Enabled Library:</strong>
                                                            Circulation, entry and exit of users, and stock verification
                                                            through RFID technology.
                                                        </li>
                                                        <li>
                                                            <strong>E-Learning Facility:</strong>
                                                            25 systems with Wi-Fi access.
                                                        </li>
                                                        <li>
                                                            <strong>Web OPAC:</strong>
                                                            Online searching facility for students and teachers.
                                                        </li>
                                                        <li>
                                                            <strong>Digital Library and Institutional Repository:
                                                            </strong>
                                                            DSpace Digital Library software.
                                                        </li>
                                                        <li>
                                                            <strong>E-Books:</strong>
                                                            40,00,000
                                                        </li>
                                                        <li>
                                                            <strong>E-Journals:</strong>
                                                            6000+ (INFLIBNET-NLIST)
                                                        </li>
                                                        <li>
                                                            <strong>Email Reminder:</strong>
                                                            Circulation due and renewal reminders.
                                                        </li>
                                                        <li>
                                                            <strong>New Arrival Display</strong>
                                                        </li>
                                                        <li>
                                                            <strong>Photocopying, Printing, and Scanning Facility
                                                            </strong>
                                                        </li>
                                                        <li>
                                                            <strong>Locker Facility</strong>
                                                        </li>
                                                        <li>
                                                            <strong>CCTV Surveillance</strong>
                                                        </li>
                                                        <li>
                                                            <strong>Career Corner:</strong>
                                                            Exclusive collection of career-oriented books and journals.
                                                        </li>
                                                        <li>
                                                            <strong>Reading Corner:</strong>
                                                            Exclusive literature collection in different languages such
                                                            as English, Malayalam, Hindi, and Arabic.
                                                        </li>
                                                        <li>
                                                            <strong>Faculty Area:</strong>
                                                            Special area for teachers.
                                                        </li>
                                                        <li>
                                                            <strong>General Reference Area:</strong>
                                                            Laptop charging facilities and broadband connection.
                                                        </li>
                                                        <li>
                                                            <strong>Software and Specific Area for Differently-abled
                                                                Students
                                                            </strong>
                                                        </li>
                                                        <li>
                                                            <strong>Plagiarism Checking Service:</strong>
                                                            URKUND software for students, teachers, and research
                                                            scholars.
                                                        </li>
                                                        <li>
                                                            <strong>Selective Dissemination of Information (SDI)
                                                                Service:
                                                            </strong>
                                                            Teachers and research scholars can register their topic of
                                                            interest in the library; they will get personalized email
                                                            alerts about new developments in their area.
                                                        </li>
                                                    </ul>
                                                    <br/>
                                                    <br/>
                                                    <strong>Activities</strong>
                                                    <br/>
                                                    <br/>
                                                    <strong>Collection</strong>
                                                    <br/>
                                                    <br/>
                                                    The major aim of an academic library is to facilitate the needs of
                                                    the student community and to develop knowledge and skills for their
                                                    future and make them able to be part of creative and innovative
                                                    society. For the career and academic growth of students; library
                                                    have a special collection in which the carrier oriented books and
                                                    journals are provided.
                                                    <br/>
                                                    <br/>
                                                    The library has a Webster’s Dictionary (35 Volume) exclusively for
                                                    Blind students with Braille, it is a rare document and preserved in
                                                    the library.
                                                    <br/>
                                                    <br/>
                                                    It also have a rare collection of Malayalam books published by
                                                    Kerala basha Institute, in which the prominent books in different
                                                    subjects such as science technology and social science in different
                                                    languages are translated to Malayalam and make them available to a
                                                    large community who doesn’t familiar with the foreign languages.
                                                    <br/>
                                                    <br/>
                                                    The major reports published by both state and central government
                                                    related to educational aspects are available in the Institutional
                                                    repository of the college library.
                                                    <br/>
                                                    <br/>
                                                    The Palm leaf engravings of Rig-Veda also available in the library.
                                                    <br/>
                                                    <table class="milestone scholar pt32 pb32" cellspacing="0"
                                                           cellpadding="7" style="width:100%;">
                                                        <thead>
                                                            <tr>
                                                                <th>
                                                                    Library resources
                                                                </th>
                                                                <th>Number</th>
                                                            </tr>
                                                        </thead>
                                                        <tbody>
                                                            <tr style="height: 24px;">
                                                                <td style="height: 24px; width: 225.133px;">Books
                                                                </td>
                                                                <td style="height: 24px; width: 122.75px;">
                                                                    40528
                                                                </td>
                                                            </tr>
                                                            <tr>
                                                                <td>Subject journals</td>
                                                                <td>40</td>
                                                            </tr>
                                                            <tr>
                                                                <td>Magazines</td>
                                                                <td>12</td>
                                                            </tr>
                                                            <tr>
                                                                <td>CD ROMs</td>
                                                                <td>187</td>
                                                            </tr>
                                                            <tr>
                                                                <td>Rare Books</td>
                                                                <td>540</td>
                                                            </tr>
                                                            <tr>
                                                                <td>Special collection(Carrier Corner)</td>
                                                                <td>1252</td>
                                                            </tr>
                                                            <tr>
                                                                <td>Project Reports.</td>
                                                                <td>9</td>
                                                            </tr>
                                                            <tr>
                                                                <td>Palm leaf engravings</td>
                                                                <td>1</td>
                                                            </tr>
                                                        </tbody>
                                                    </table>
                                                    <strong>E Resources and Institutional Repository</strong>
                                                    <br/>
                                                    <br/>
                                                    Electronic resources (or e-resources) are materials in digital
                                                    format accessible electronically. e-resources are electronic
                                                    journals (e-journal), electronic books (e-book) online databases in
                                                    varied digital formats are maintained in the library.
                                                    <br/>
                                                    <br/>
                                                    Using D Space an open source institutional repository library aid
                                                    the management and dissemination of the increasingly copious amount
                                                    of scholarly electronic resources produced by academics.
                                                    <br/>
                                                    <br/>
                                                    N-List E-Books:<a href="http://nlist.inflibnet.ac.in/">
                                                    http://nlist.inflibnet.ac.in/
                                                </a>40.00,000+
                                                    <br/>
                                                    <table class="milestone scholar pt32 pb32"
                                                           style="width:100%;">
                                                        <thead>
                                                            <tr>
                                                                <th>
                                                                    E-Resorces
                                                                </th>
                                                                <th>Number</th>
                                                            </tr>
                                                        </thead>
                                                        <tbody>
                                                            <tr style="height: 24px;">
                                                                <td>N-List E-Journals:
                                                                    <a href="http://nlist.inflibnet.ac.in/">
                                                                        http://nlist.inflibnet.ac.in/
                                                                    </a>
                                                                </td>
                                                                <td style="height: 24px; width: 122.75px;">
                                                                    6000+
                                                                </td>
                                                            </tr>
                                                            <tr>
                                                                <td>Shodganga:
                                                                    <a href="http://shodhganga.inflibnet.ac.in/">
                                                                        http://shodhganga.inflibnet.ac.in/
                                                                    </a>
                                                                </td>
                                                                <td>223971 thesis</td>
                                                            </tr>
                                                            <tr>
                                                                <td>ShodaSindhu:
                                                                    <a href=" https://www.inflibnet.ac.in/ess/">
                                                                        https://www.inflibnet.ac.in/ess/
                                                                    </a>
                                                                </td>
                                                                <td>10000+ journals 31350000+ e books</td>
                                                            </tr>
                                                            <tr>
                                                                <td>Shod Gangotri:
                                                                    <a href="https://shodhgangotri.inflibnet.ac.in/">
                                                                        https://shodhgangotri.inflibnet.ac.in/
                                                                    </a>
                                                                </td>
                                                                <td>6450 synopsis</td>
                                                            </tr>
                                                            <tr>
                                                                <td>ePG Pathshala:
                                                                    <a href="https://epgp.inflibnet.ac.in/">
                                                                        https://epgp.inflibnet.ac.in/
                                                                    </a>
                                                                </td>
                                                                <td>70 subjects</td>
                                                            </tr>
                                                            <tr>
                                                                <td>DOAJ:
                                                                    <a href="https://doaj.org/">https://doaj.org/</a>
                                                                </td>
                                                                <td>12980</td>
                                                            </tr>
                                                            <tr>
                                                                <td>J-Gate:
                                                                    <a href="https://jgateplus.com/home/">
                                                                        https://jgateplus.com/home/
                                                                    </a>
                                                                </td>
                                                                <td>50,164</td>
                                                            </tr>
                                                            <tr>
                                                                <td>International journal of Biological Sciences:
                                                                    <a href="http://www.ijbs.com/">
                                                                        http://www.ijbs.com/
                                                                    </a>
                                                                </td>
                                                                <td>1</td>
                                                            </tr>
                                                            <tr>
                                                                <td>J-Store:
                                                                    <a href="https://www.jstor.org/">
                                                                        https://www.jstor.org/
                                                                    </a>
                                                                </td>
                                                                <td>20,00,000+</td>
                                                            </tr>
                                                            <tr>
                                                                <td>OAIster:
                                                                    <a href="https://www.oclc.org/en/oaister.html">
                                                                        https://www.oclc.org/en/oaister.html
                                                                    </a>
                                                                </td>
                                                                <td>70,00000+</td>
                                                            </tr>
                                                            <tr>
                                                                <td>PubChem:
                                                                    <a href="https://pubchem.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/">
                                                                        https://pubchem.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/
                                                                    </a>
                                                                </td>
                                                                <td>123535</td>
                                                            </tr>
                                                            <tr>
                                                                <td>RePEc:
                                                                    <a href="http://repec.org/">http://repec.org/</a>
                                                                </td>
                                                                <td>3000+</td>
                                                            </tr>
                                                            <tr>
                                                                <td>Spriger LinK:
                                                                    <a href="https://link.springer.com/">
                                                                        https://link.springer.com/
                                                                    </a>
                                                                </td>
                                                                <td>324</td>
                                                            </tr>
                                                            <tr>
                                                                <td>NISCAIR Journals:
                                                                    <a href="https://www.niscair.res.in/sciencecommunication/researchjournals/rejour/rejour1-del.htm/">
                                                                        https://www.niscair.res.in/sciencecommunication/researchjournals/rejour/rejour1-del.htm
                                                                    </a>
                                                                </td>
                                                                <td>16</td>
                                                            </tr>
                                                            <tr>
                                                                <td>DRDO Journals:
                                                                    <a href="https://www.drdo.gov.in/drdo/English/index.jsp?pg=journals.jsp">
                                                                        https://www.drdo.gov.in/drdo/English/index.jsp?pg=journals.jsp
                                                                    </a>
                                                                </td>
                                                                <td>3</td>
                                                            </tr>
                                                        </tbody>
                                                    </table>
                                                    <strong>Library Committee</strong>
                                                    <br/>
                                                    <br/>
                                                    A Library Advisory Committee has been constituted with Six senior
                                                    faculty members representing different disciplines, Librarian as the
                                                    Coordinator and Principle as the Chairman
                                                </div>
                                                <iframe loading="lazy" style="border: 0;"
                                                        src="https://www.google.com/maps/embed?pb=!1m18!1m12!1m3!1d3916.6444341260226!2d76.43661282039488!3d10.99018811098465!2m3!1f0!2f0!3f0!3m2!1i1024!2i768!4f13.1!3m3!1m2!1s0x3ba7d5a16aaaaaab%3A0xf0df686ddb8b1045!2sM.E.S+Kalladi+College!5e0!3m2!1sen!2sin!4v1477896577791"
                                                        width="100%" height="300px" frameborder="0"
                                                        allowfullscreen="allowfullscreen"></iframe>
                                            </div>
                                        </div>
                                        <div class=" col-md-3">
                                            <div style="padding:40px 0;text-align: center;font-size: 20px;">
                                                <strong>College Librarian</strong>
                                            </div>
                                            <div class="faculties pt32" style="height:auto;">
                                                <div class="faculty_img">
                                                    <img src="/mes_college/static/img/faculty.jpg"
                                                         class="w-100 h-100" style="object-fit:contain;"/>
                                                </div>
                                                <div class="faculty_name">
                                                    FAIZUNNIZA Y
                                                </div>
                                                <div class="designation">College Librarian
                                                </div>
                                                <span style="font-size:12px;">MLIS, B.Ed, UGC NET
                                                </span>
                                                <br/>
                                                <span style="font-size:12px;">faizun.sameer@gmail.com 8078869557
                                                </span>
                                            </div>
                                            <div style="padding-top:20px;">
                                                <strong>Library Assistant:
                                                </strong>
                                                T.Usman
                                                <br/>
                                                <strong>Library Assistant:</strong>
                                                T.P.
                                                Abdul
                                                Kareem
                                            </div>
                                        </div>
                                    </div>

                                </div>
                            </section>
                        </div>
                    </t>
                </t>
            </field>
        </record>
        <record id="library_page" model="website.page">
            <field name="url">/library</field>
            <field name="is_published">True</field>
            <field name="view_id" ref="library"/>
            <field name="track">True</field>
        </record>
    </data>
</odoo>